A temple whose study is more than
other schools
it dont only make promises.
It also fulfils them
no matter its building is old
than other schools
but its study is much better than
other schools
and the whole credit goes to its
principal
i dont have any other way
dont you think prayer was so long?
Do you know principal call me
in the cabin at 5 pm
he call all of us
by blood pressure becomes low
by hearing his name
you haven't done your home work?
Did you come to school late?
Then why you are scaring like student?
Will everything be fine?
Last time when you took my fine,
you did not return it
you can see college outside
but now you are in my class.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Go and sit at your place
how much you will take to sit?
What he said?
He is saying bench
you wont understand.
Sit down
that is not my bench.
This is my bench
this is my bench
what are you looking at?
You will take time to understand me
who has doubt?
All have doubt
what is going on here?
Students are enjoying?
Dont you feel shame?
You are dancing like monkey
go and do your work
go and give tea to principal
if management comes in my hand then
i will throw everyone
who is pushing management?
Its too late
is this the age to come at school?
Where is principal cabin?
Today i join as a teacher
still peoples are angry on english
teacher because of english man
your qualification is more than
your age
its your firstjob but i believe
you will do it
you also know music
change your hobby into profession.
School also needs a music teacher
if i'm not sure about anything
then i dont do it
as i come today so i will
start work from today
come in the staff meeting at 5 pm
send sharma inside
and its become life style for me now
you are right
principal still not come
check my heartbeat
principal is coming
he is a new teacher
i joined this school 32 years ago
on that time there were about
30 to 35 schools
and we were on top
now there are 350 to 400 schools
still our school name is in history
i dont like people talking about past
as a sports teacher, the management give you
facilities... are you happy with them?
It needs some make over
its just a dream
when you joined this school?
What did you want?
I can do anything for students
if i send you foreign for studies then
you would do more better
you think this for me...
thats enough for me
i think this for me but this thinking
is a question for me
it was taking three times more fees
on that time
and i think its taking 10 times
more than us
its a very small school than ours
still all parents are willing to
get admission in that school
people are ready to give any amount
as a donation
i have heard they use digital black board
they use many high tech facilities that
we cant compete
we are still behind than many schools
management is making a plan
i will inform you through email
with whom?
Its not like that
if you scare than tell me
its time for my class,
i'm going
school time is over
i wanna talk to you
i joined last year mid term
there is no problem. I have given
my job application in USA
how was your 1st day?
I think i have to work hard
i think school needs funds
will i get the salary?
Our principal thinks about school alot
thats why he is very stressed
he is also going to USA
just look at you
we all thought...
i must be a very old age person
principal talked to you about music
yes he was saying...
but you said you cant do
they are just childrens
until now i just teach english
without asking you i promised
students that tomorrow there will be a music class
its ok.
I will tell them
i'm getting late for my class.
Students are waiting for me. Later
where are you going?
Nothing happen to students
come on sleep
who is there?
Who is there?
What happen?
Why you are crying?
You fight with him?
No i didn't
then why you are crying?
I think all 3 toilets are occupied
go into my room
nothing.
Go
you like painting
if you keep look there than you
will be involve in colors
be in your limit
you are continuously looking at natasha
he sings well
when you took it?
Keep the phone inside
you are my friend?
Will you do one work for me?
Can you find out how old is
rahul sir?
I was kidding.
You eat
dont worry
he wont bite him.
Its his friend
all students are playing together are
he is sitting here
he name is Parth.
He is a very nice boy
he dont have any friend
he made a puppy his friend.
He daily plays with him
he is a very sweet boy
put this on my desk
recess is finished
go inside
did you read the email of principal?
Yes i was reading it
he better know what he want
did you read principal email?
I forget.
I check it now
we will do discussion there
1st time i'm feeling negative
in our school there are 40
students in one class
which is better than other schools
how students will study?
Then where we will getjob?
What do you think?
He did not left any option for us
i hope all teachers are agree with us
i have talked to all teachers
they all are with us
i like you have come
first take care of yourself
you are right.
School has become for good than before
answer of your email is negative
now what will we do?
Your teachers are also not with you
they clearly said no
i will talk to them
i have some more options
but one girls know what she should
give to rahul sir
what is in it?
Also give him football
leave the football
go and sit at your place
why you are not doing practice?
What happen?
I'm distributing football to your
students
can you tell me who decide this that
who will play and who wont?
If they wont buy ball from school than
they cant play here
its their balls
if its their than play at their house
if you dont know the rules of game
then dont involve in it
you know the rules of game and i
know the rules of school
they are my best players
you go from here.
I will talk to principal
he will come back at 4 days
you will talk to him.
But i have a request
stop playing football with
management
dont disturb me
do you know what is combo meal?
We also have to buy cold drink
and chips
what are you doing here?
Go and distribute these coupons
you deny this?
Whom you ask this?
What is the thing to ask in it?
You care about students health but
you dont care about school health
what is loss in it?
I tell you the logic
school can save Rs 6 per bottle
you can sell all 4 in market
we have to use atleast one container
its a legal matter. Dont involve in this.
Read this
i'm tired.
Dont ask me
tomorrow i want all the papers
play as loud as you can
play it
play it loud
what is going on here?
They are playing
who give them guitars?
Your all questions answer are in it
you dont like childrens?
I like them but you can only
see these childrens
but i can see those students too
can you see those students happy?
Have you ever played guitar?
You have to learn it.
These childrens cant hold guitar even
how can we calm down?
Its a management decision
you put this on each other
we dont know whether they are
running school or shop?
Principal is coming tomorrow.
We will talk to him
what are you doing?
Now you started thinking?
I told him to stand here
whats in your hand?
Water? If you give him water than
i wont give you water
i have come now
you are not going good
i dont care where you will bring us
but before going anywhere have
a look at this
its a supreme court order that any
private school can increase its fees
your son forgets everything.
He did not bring the fees
he was not ignoring
he knows i dont have money thats
why he did not tell me
i just give him some punishment and
you come here
i have manage to arrange his school fees
we are asking just more
you need time?
You will get time
are you kidding?
Thanks you remind me my position
i thought will childrens will study
in big school
what are you doing?
I'm doing my work
your religion tells you this?
You understand one thing
explain me one small thing?
This month i will do
i dont understand this
you cant understand this
cut his fees from my salary
we wanna talk to you alone
sharma go outside
thank god you have come back
or sharma was about to sell school
he is right.
He misbehave with everyone
please stop sharma
do think sharma has that power and mind
that he can do this?
He is doing on my instructions
i also want co-operation from you
i cant see this
he is right
he is the most senior here.
I will also do the same
why you call all of us here?
I know what happened between you
and principal
but one thing is clear.
You cant understand one thing
you saw whatever happened there
thats why we have to do this
resignation is not the solution of problem
if principal will take action against
us then?
Atleast talk positive
if they take resignation then?
It wont happen
if all teachers resign together than
how a school will run?
Principal and management this
more far than you
new teacher willl come in place of you
they will do as management will say
i'm a poor guy.
Thats why i'm peon in school
i study only 5 class
since school is made,
i'm here
many students came here
think something for these childrens.
You are well educated, you can think
because of this your school fees will be increased
we will increase your school
reputation
i dont understand anything
may i explain this?
Have you ever heard the name of
this school?
Its in nasik.
Have you ever been to nasik?
This school generate 1.5 crore revenure
and they are planning for college too
we need your support
dont you think it will effect
studies?
Students will be tired
trust me students will enjoy
from now you wont learn
music
but why?
We will meet a special person
but one this he will
do like us
what?
Lets see who make him friend first?
He made puppy his friend
how can he make so many puppies
his friend?
He dont know how to do
friendship
they only listen to heart
it means Parth heart is better than
all of us
will you be my friend?
We all are your friend
if anyone say anything to you
then we will beat him
students are ready,
sharma tell them to do fast
they are ready
its a technical matter.
He have to manage the focus
go and do the coverage
give this to all
what happen?
Did you get hurt?
Take him to dispensary
they are doing practice since long time,
they are tired
students are not stars
do you know who they are
in which newspaper you write?
They write in all newspaper
did you hear?
They are about to write
its enough.
We are getting insulted
stop pulling.
Go and take the photo
but lets try one more time
you have done this
dont talk much or i will
beat you
tomorrow they will come
you are our super hero
we tried very hard but they
did not take our photo
sir told us they will be in 2 days
then sing correctly
how are you?
I will talk to you later
what is your name?
I can understand your and
your students excitement
i do this daily
that one sir
come out
we did reharsal together
can we take him?
He is good
if you like him than take
him home
dont misbehave with childrens
give chance to everyone
you have done your work.
You teach them
let us do our work.
You are not doing good
you are also separating their combinations
you will lose their competitions.
They will lose
do you this for reality show?
Its just a drama
we need a talent.
Butjust for asking vote
everybody sing well but people like
singer who can ask votes well
i cant understand this
but i can understand them
treat them well.
They are trying their best to impress you
if you need help then i can help you
you teach them this?
They are your winners?
Who will come on stage to stop them crying
i wont go without you
study is going on
its also a part of studies
i was saying that its a part of studies
your son picture will be publish
in newspaper
do you understand?
I have to manage many files?
Will you come with me in
party tonight?
Do one thing give me your everything
and you take the respect
you are not looking well
you are sweating too
sharma is standing downstairs
how long we have to do this?
Let these girls go from here,
and let us go from here
your shot and hero is there.
What we are doing here?
I'm telling you go to your place
dont worry.
Let me talk to them
you wanna study today?
Bring the degree today
go and stand there
if you wont stand here then you
cant be in school anymore
come fast.
I'm hungry
he cant speak sponsors name
correctly
i practiced alot in night
but he told this name now
is it necessary to say sponsors name?
Press and media are outside
you wanted this?
Do you know the meaning of trustee?
What you did so that all students
go for strike?
Its a public question
i'm the principal of this school
i'm the responsible for this
and for this i'm resigining
do you wanna ask anything?
All students want this
they are standing here because i know the truth
and i want you to tell them truth
i can understand
they are your power
tell them truth
nothing will happen
until now you were fighting alone.
Now we will fight together
all come here to become student
only 2 professions students select
in my time
doctor or engineer
i dont wanted to share my time
thats why i did not marry
i know everyone with their names
i'm from Sarasvati Study Temple.
I'm in army now
i'm the manager of this company
i feel very good.
Nothing is better than this
i never think its a business.
Its always a profession for me
now this profession has become
business
we have to update everything. No matter
thinking is updated or not.
Its not a 5 star hotel
you are showing me the same
accounts since last 4 years
world has changed
competition is increased
many schools has become business
our school's reputation is much better
if you dont give me much profit then
i will close down school
dont hope for any payment from me
try somewhere else
i went to many banks and finance companies
but i did not lose hope
i'm aditya sahaye
your name is not in today's list.
I have appointment
sir is going overseas for 2 months,
you come after that
all hopes were ended
i wanted to share this with you
but i thought you dont have much power
you have more power than me
i know you got problem because of me
same problem was happenning with me
please forgive me
i dont had any profit in it
i dont know how 32 years passed
strike come to an end
sad thing is that principal has resigned
but we will remember his thoughts
i left something here.
Thats why i come here to collect
by your age and experience,
you are great
this school needs a principal
tell the staff that there is a meeting
in my office at 5 pm
ok lets meet at 5 pm in meeting room