Sir..
Susanna Anna Marie Johannes-
Prima facie, suicide
She set ablaze not only
herself but her mansion too
Married to 6 men, and
strangely all of them dead.
She must have been one hell of a lay
Well..
I'm sure you've seen
what we've recovered..
Skull, some bones,
ash, make up kit etc
We need to carry out DNA profiling.
Hope you're not too busy?
I'll do it.
It's a priority case
and the police want to
ensure that she's dead.
Arun..
What are you doing?
How come you never
showed this to me?
Why?
Secret?
Is this 'the Susanna'?
''Saheb.'' [Master]
Now, she's no more.
Detached from life,
and torn apart by love..
My ''Saheb'' was melancholic.
All her life, she was in
search for her eternal love.
She was very lonely.
Just an infant when
she lost her mother..
And before she could become
an adult, her father died.
My senior ''Saheb''. [Her father]
He was her everything!
Friend, mother, and brother.
And after he was gone..
.. she tried hard to find
him in every man she could.
On the day of her father's funeral..
.. in full black attire, she
reminded me of soft snow..
.. rolling off the
mountain in the silent night.
No wonder she radiated in black.
And soon, it became her colour.
Uncle Goonga!
Too much to say, but
unfortunately born dumb.
I was born an orphan!
Don't know if he
adopted me or I adopted him.
My first real competition.
And senior ''Saheb's'' last wish.
The first husband..
Major Edwin Rodriques.
Goonga!
How much longer?
Ghalib!
What in the devil is he saying?
He says, everything should be
ready in the next half an hour.
I don't want to see
any of his rats around.
Ghalib.
Poet by name, butler by profession
and mocks a Bollywood villain.
Anything else, sir?
What did he say?
Thank you, sir!
If he knew you were calling him
a fucker he'd pull your eyes out.
Ghalib!
- Sir!
The third ace in her trio.
Maggie aunty!
Under whose care ''Saheb'' grew up.
She became her mother
and her best friend.
She had a few other friends too.
Venomous, dangerous..
.. but faithful like no other.
It's a Derby, darling!
The jockey is as
important as the stallion.
I don't see any
reason for change, Rod.
Goonga was daddy's
favourite jockey.
What do you think, Martha?
I'm think someone here
may have a better idea.
Right, Tim?
What do you have to say, Mr. Rangan?
Why don't we hire a
professional rider from abroad?
We can afford it and
I know one in Prague.
Affordability was
never an issue, Mr. Rangan.
Professional jockey from Prague..
You boy
What do you think you're doing?
Stealing!
Come here.
Come on.
Show me your hands!
Come on!
Whose rascal is this?
I picked a few for Candy, Sir.
Who's Candy?
Your new horse.
That's a nice name for a horse.
Candy.
He runs fast when he eat it Sir.
How much have you studied?
Seven and a half.
Anything else?
Yes, ''Saheb''. Candy loves you.
You tik-tok-tik-tok..
him in race, and win 'Dabry'!
Miss ''Saheb'', forgive me!
Thought I'd help this orphan.
Will send this fool
back to the village.
You won't see this rat anymore.
You're right!
He won't be seen here anymore.
Because he'll be
starting school tomorrow.
Okay.
Sugar.
''Saheb'', thank you!
Snap! My life
changed in a split second.
''Saheb'' picked me up
from a bed of thorns..
and placed me on a bed of roses.
This is the new
admission I was talking about.
She was my goddess.
And I her blind devotee.
All said and done Arun, the
Major was pretty handsome.
Quite a dashing fellow.
The perfect Indian husband.
Boring, possessive,
insecure and a doubting Thomas.
And a fart king too.
Mr. Stinker!
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention please.
Here's to our very own,
Major Edwin Rodriques.
The recipient of
the gallantry award.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
We salute the bravery
and courage you displayed
all throughout operation Blue Star.
It took a heavy toll on our brigade
and on your company in particular.
And my leg!
Hey beautiful!
I can't figure out if you're
getting older or younger by the day.
Edwin is greying fast
but you look the same.
Thank you!
Here, for your
beautiful better half.
She's quit drinking.
Really, since when?
Today, I quit every morning.
And that Brigadier Venkat, is
the secret of my beauty! Cheers!
Cheers!
Good evening, sir!
- Good evening.
May I have the pleasure of a dance..
.. with the lady..
I always had two left feet.
Now I've lost one.
Really!
You're quite the dancer, lieutenant.
Sir.
But no match to your
beautiful half, sir.
Beautiful half.
And the better one too.
And she has a
beautiful name as well.
Susanna.
What?
But you can call her..
Mrs. Rodriques, if you please.
Thank you.
You know you can't
handle the fucking alcohol.
''I quit every morning.''
Stop fluttering around.
You're a married woman.
Are you ashamed to be my wife?
Then why?
Why do you keep
reminding me of my disability?
I'm sorry.
It's high time we had a child.
Once you're a mother,
you'll learn wifely duties too.
Did you visit the gynaecologist?
All tests are normal.
Then why can't you conceive?
The doctor says, there's
nothing wrong with me.
So now..
I'm disabled in bed too?
''I've come from Alabama,
with a banjo on my knee.. ''
''Oh Susanna! Won't
you cry for me.. ''
How often have I told you
to knock before entering?
Knock, knock!
Next time, I'll bury you alive.
This was bound to happen,
my friends!
Marry in a haste and..
Repent at leisure.
You want to break his other leg?
Don't fuck around with him.
At the end of the day,
you'll be the one to be fucked.
Sir! Are you alright?
You bastard!
Son of a bitch.
So you want to fight?
Goonga.. Goonga..
Goonga.. what happened?
What happened?
Ghalib.. Ghalib!
He will survive.
But we're sorry, we
couldn't save his eye.
One eye is enough to
witness what's going to happen.
The next time I saw the
Major for the last time.
Going in search of
the man-eating panther.
Can I also have a drink tonight?
Just a drink?
No.
Minimum three.
And you should be fun!
We must be very still, very quiet..
.. or the animal won't come.
The beast in me is already here.
Major sir.
Major sir, panther.
The panther wasn't
interested in the goat.
He was looking for humans.
Can't tell whether the
Major lost his balance..
Or whether someone pushed him.
Nevertheless..
it took the forest officials
two days to find the Major..
.. or whatever was left of him.
I just couldn't get
myself to mourn for the Major.
Had fate given me another chance..
.. to woo my ''Saheb''?
Like a balloon my
hopes went soaring.
But she chose the guitar instead.
Indian women fall for a
guitarist over a riff.
And this asshole had
the vocal chords too.
Before the wedding this creature
was called Jamshed Singh Rathod.
From now I'm Jimmy.
Jimmy Stetson.
You can call me Jim.
And you call me.. Susie.
Jim and Susie!
Susie and Jim!
Made for each other, that's right!
''Her lips were ripe and so close''
''O Mama''
''I looked at them and all but froze''
You wrote this for me?
No, it sprung from within.
My wedding gift to you.
''O Mama''
''My heart now only
thinks from the heart''
''O Mama''
''My heart often bangs my head''
''No stranger to me''
''May my fall be her rise''
''She, my nemesis, too,
is no stranger to me''
''A beating heart
forever stays beaten''
''O Mama''
''O Mama, she shoots at me''
''this marble-eyed meow-like girl''
''O Mama''
''She steals on me, not
a sound she makes.. ''
''O Mama''
''She smuggles herself into my
dreams, pray it doesn't stay a dream''
''O Mama''
''There isn't hope''
''But hope remains, still''
''How I languish in
the anguish of love''
''Something's being ripped out of me''
''O Mama''
''O Mama, she shoots at me''
''this marble-eyed meow-like girl''
''O Mama''
Welcome back to
''Cultivation Today''..
''She's taken on the reign,
this world is her's not mine.. ''
''O Mama''
''How do I believe her love,
it's undefined''
''O Mama''
''Should've let the light inside''
''For my heart and mind divide''
''Have you lost me to her spell''
''O Mama''
''Won't you help me''
Okay that's enough!
What's the proof this is yours?
This was my college composition.
Jamshed was the backup
vocalist in my band.
Bloody robber.
Where the hell is he? Call him.
Here's proof.
It first came out in English, now
they're launching the holy version.
''O Mother.. O Mother.. ''
Which record label?
Now what?
Respect.
Shall we?
Thanks man! Here's
a new composition.
Interested?
''At heart, the heart's just a heart''
''Full of tricks and illusions,
Simply a smooth operator''
''The heart's heady at
times and at times, take heart''
''Full of tricks and illusions,
Simply a smooth operator''
''The heart's heady at
times and at times, take heart''
''It's just a gentle whisper,
at times and at times.. ''
.. an uproarious drumroll''
''At times, it's the raging fire
pulsating in your veins at times..''
''.. it is the calming coolness''
''Believe it or not''
''Is only a matter of the heart''
''At heart, the heart's a heart''
''The shore for drowning men''
''The ignorance of the boor''
''A hundred heavens,
that's what it's worth''
''At heart, the heart's a heart''
Where are you, boss?
The Berlin wall has collapsed..
.. and so has the government.
And you're stuck on cocaine?
This is what you call heroin!
No one has the balls to
behave in this manner.
This is Bappi's song!
You know how many
musicians are waiting for him?
A hundred! Who is going to pay?
Your father?
''At heart, the heart's a heart''
Ladies and gentlemen,
Jimmy will be here soon.
Please remain calm.
He will be here soon.
Please remain calm, please.
In a few moments he will be here.
''A heart which beats.. ''
''At heart, the heart's a heart''
Yes, who is it.. ?
What do you want?
Yes..
I'm sorry.. Jimmy?
Jimmy..
Jimmy boy, you've got a fan here.
Got you.
- Bang you!
Bang, bang, bang!
FBI, dead! CBI, dead!
Jimmy has the power!
- No, we are still alive.
Jimmy is a cheater!
Susie.. what are you doing here?
Susie..
When did you come?
Why didn't you inform me?
Susie, don't misunderstand.
They are just friends!
Just..
- Friends.
We were playing a game!
Cops and robbers!
You wanna play?
Jimmy is a robber..
Hey FBI cheater.
Cops and robbers!
Bang, bang, bang!
FBI, dead! CBI, dead!
I got you. I got you.
You die. You die. You die.
This time she was determined..
.. to save her marriage.
This time she wouldn't give up.
Susie, remember..
It's Jim.
Your Jim.
Why are you doing this to me?
I won't go back to drugs!
I swear.
Please, Susie!
You bitch!
I will choke you to
death once I'm free.
You are messing with
Jamshed Singh Rathod.
I am of royal blood.
I will cut you into tiny
pieces and feed you to the dogs.
You bitch!
Susie..
I can recommend a good
rehab facility in Bangalore..
.. very private, excellent one.
No, doctor.
I can't leave him alone.
He is my life.
By now Saheb's
life began to settle..
Jimmy was getting better.
But she didn't realise
that drugs addicts..
.. become sly once they're caught.
'Champions of deception.'
Sir..
Madame.
This was confiscated from
a drug peddler yesterday.
Who else could own
such a beautiful piece?
I knew, as soon as
I laid eyes on it!
It's priceless too.. how much?
You never put a price on
priceless things, Inspector.
''Keemat.'' [Price]
Inspector Keemat Lal.
Muzzle loader NX 6.
Amongst the first guns
to be brought to India..
.. by the soldiers
of the British rule.
Was a favourite in my
father's antique collection.
I'd like to question your servants.
A marble-eyed meow-like girl..
O doggy..
Our servants are
more loyal than owners.
Madame..
Thank you.
Madame.
You can call me by my name,
if you please..
Susanna.
How dare I.. Madame.
Thank you. Nevertheless..
I don't think I would ever..
maybe another time.
Right now.. it's not appropriate.
Jim..
Careful, sir!
These snakes are venomous.
The snake temple.
Snake temple?
But, Madame is a Christian.
Yes, she is!
Her father was a Christian,
but mother, a Hindu.
She set it up.
Saheb feeds them milk,
every morning without fail!
How?
- She goes down.
Isn't she scared?
No! They're her pets.
She thinks humans
are more poisonous.
Wow!
That's great.
Sir, snake!
Are you alright, sir?
- Yes, I'm fine.
One, two, three, four, five, six..
Six, five, four, three, two, one..
Whose footprint is this?
Could be anyone's..
Notjust anyone..
It belongs to the murderer.
Murderer?
Is anyone left?
- Yes, there is.
Who is it?
It's me.
Why do you bother, Madame.
You've gotten your feet all muddy!
There is no need, Madame.
Not Madame, Susanna.
You are just.. I mean.. how will I..
Really.. I mean.. I mean..
Joking!
Not right. Who am I to say!
Just as you wish.. the next time.
But it's fine.. not a bad thing.
I'll try next time.
But how will I?
It is believed that Jesus
spent his last days in Kashmir.
''Saheb'' left for Kashmir
in search of the Lord..
Instead of Jesus,
she met ''Mohammed''.
Hail Allah!
Mohammed Wasiullah Khan.
A.K. A The Traveller.
From the soot of
spiraling everyday smoke..
.. a patch of sky,
now remains blackened..
.. all day long.
Great!
- Wonderful!
Do not bow your head beneath it..
.. for now when you prostrate,
God yanks His feet away.
In the mounds of rotting rubbish..
.. heads of bodies
gone cold still smoulder.
Wonderful! Wonderful!
Hungry four legged animals, fight
over the bones of arms and legs.
The flesh and the bone
belongs to the one..
.. who first digs its
teeth into the flesh.
May I proceed?
- Yes, please.
The flesh and the bone
belongs to the one..
.. who first digs its
teeth into the flesh.
The men of faith now ask, who
first dug his spade into this earth!
Wow!
- Wonderful! - Wonderful!
The men of faith now ask, who
first dug his spade into this earth!
Some say there was
a mosque here once.
Some say no, once a
temple stood here.
Wow! Wow!
- Wonderful!
But when you touch your
forehead to the ground..
God yanks His feet away now.
He cannot bring Himself to believe..
.. that He once called
this place, His home.
Wow!
- Wow!
This time, ''Saheb'' not
only had a new lover..
.. but also a new name and religion.
Susanna Anna Marie
Johannes was now..
Sultana Wasiullah Khan.
Thank you.
Wow!
- Wow! - Great!
- One more, please!
Don't go!
One more verse!
My next verse..
- Yes, please.
A day shall dawn..
.. bringing with it a calm..
.. the heart bereft of desires,
the mind devoid of passion..
''Shoreless, totally fathomless''
''Close your eyes, please''
''I have been drowning''
''I need to breathe''
''Shoreless, totally fathomless,
Close your eyes, please''
''I have been drowning,
I need to breathe''
''Lillah!''
''Turn your face away from me''
''It'll be a great kindness''
''Ever since I have seen you''
''My breath's stuck''
''Shoreless, totally fathomless''
''Close your eyes, please''
''I have been drowning''
''I need to breathe''
May I?
- Proceed.
If a flitting glance of yours,
were to graze me
That would be greeting enough..
.. and I'll keep my
eyes forever lowered.
Wow!
Ever since I have seen you
My breath is..
Stuck!
- Brilliant!
Mukarrar!
Who is that?
Your uncle!
''Pray, take a look''
''At your feet''
''Something's stuck, it seems''
''Please ask Time to move on''
''If a flitting glance of yours''
''Were to graze me''
''That would be greeting enough..''
''.. And I'll keep my
eyes forever lowered''
''At your feet''
''Ever since I have seen you''
''My breath's stuck''
''Shoreless, totally fathomless''
''Close your eyes, please''
''I have been drowning''
''I need to breathe''
''Lillah!''
Tender and romantic in his poetry..
.. bastard in bed.
Unless he beat the
shit out of the woman..
he remained impotent.
Come on..
Come on, bit me.
I like it.
It's great fun.
Initially she tried hard
to conceal her scars..
.. but her wounds grew deeper.
Love became a myth.
Like a mirage.
You think it's there,
but it really isn't.
Prayers, offerings and sacrifices,
she tried it all.
But nothing worked.
Is it coming from
the heart or the being?
These fumes, from
where do they come?
Love is a heavy stone..
Not for the weak ones.
What does 'Natawan' mean?
''Debilitated.''
Weak..
Feeble.
Sultana!
Cold-blooded!
Why kill someone?
She could've left him and come home.
Who would've stopped her?
As a child, Miss
''Saheb'' would walk to school.
There were two paths.
Both equidistant.
No difference at all.
And one day, there came a crazy dog,
Who scared her every single day.
She could've taken the other path.
She hid her father's
Mouser in her bag..
And bang!
''Saheb'' always gets her way..
And the dogs are blown off!
Ladies and gentlemen,
to present the trophy..
may I now call on stage, our
esteemed guest of honour..
Mr. Nikolai Vronsky.
Science-attaché to the
Russian consulate, Sir.
Thank you, sir.
Greetings!
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm here to
handover this wonderful trophy..
to the winner, but before I do so..
I really would like to
share something with you.
I did bet on this particular horse..
and I won a fortune.
I need to say thank you very much.
I'm grateful to you.
I am Vronsky..
Nikolai Vronsky.
Then I must be Anna!
Anna Karenina is my
favorite character.
I've read the novel, I
don't know.. so many times.
In Hindi.. please.
I'm learning the language.
What else have you picked up?
Okay!
My love for you is eternal.
Let's go, Saheb.
Mr. Vronsky, have you
met my pal here, Arun.
- Is that your full name?
- Yes! Arun.. Arun Kumar.
Anna..
- Anna? - Hold on!
Please have dinner with me..
.. at a nice restaurant today.
I am very rich.
I'm sorry, what?
I mean to say that..
I really would like to
spend this play money on..
.. a nice dinner, somewhere?
Would you please do it to me?
I'm sorry, Mr. Vronsky, I
have a prior engagement.
I do definitely understand that,
but can I at least..
Anna!
Can I at least drop
you to.. your mansion?
Please!
I have my car.
But I have
something better, a mother.
Amitabh Bachchan.
From the movie, Deewar.
It's destiny.
What?
From now on..
no English, no Campa Cola.
Only Russian and Vodka.
Russia and me.. why?
Because you my friend,
are headed to Russia.
To study at St.
Petersburg Medical Academy.
Cheers!
Why?
Because, Nik loves me..
and I love you, my little sugar.
Nik!
To hell I'm going to Russia!
Why not?
Because, I hate vodka.
It's because..
.. you are jealous of the Russians.
Quiet a distance he has walked
A thousand distant miles
Another Pushkin from Russia
Who's left Moscow only
to be with me
Something like this is
possible only in love
Darling
Let your eyes feast on mine
Darling let the passion rush
Don't hold it back
let this love gush
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it back
let this love gush
The Spring's joyless
The beloved's heart's restless
Hold back the songbirds
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Anna?
That hillock enveloped in mist
Where the fairies once lived
You'll find it
across the high Khyber
That's what all
the fairies still say
Darling
I'm merely a serf, let
me groom the Princess
Let this restless
heart steal a little solace
Let me conquer the
heart of my beloved
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
The Spring's joyless
The beloved's heart's restless
Hold back the songbirds
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it back
let this love gush
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it back
let this love gush
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Honey..
Good evening, darling!
Did you have to leave
all the guests alone..
by themselves?
Come on back in.
Who were you talking to, Nik?
A colleague, from Moscow.
Woman?
Oh you're so jealous!
Look at me. So jealous!
What do you think?
Your last words of the
conversation meant..
'Darling, I will be back soon.'
Your Russian is so bad.
Shall we just go in,
please? Come on.
You are hiding
something from me, Nik.
No!
Sure?
No.
When I say I go to Kanyakumari..
I don't go to Kanyakumari.
I go to Koodankulam, instead.
Koodankulam?
Yes, Koodankulam.
Koodankulam Nuclear Power project.
Honey, we're helping
your government to..
set up the light water
reactor technology in India.
Excuse me?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means your country, is going to
become one of the self sufficient..
nuclear states.
Nik.
You are a spy?
Come on!
No.
No!
I am your friend.
And..
my love for you is eternal.
A kilo of this, please.
I'm just not ready
for another marriage.
Why not?
Marriage is the worst
thing that happened to mankind.
And in any case..
I want to remain in love, you know.
Me too.
But you know I..
I can't stay for long with you.
Unless I marry you.
Why? Marriage why?
Because..
I'm pregnant..
.. with your child.
A shocking incident..
India had finally
accomplished its nuclear test.
And instead of Hiroshima,
it was now, my heart!
Saheb dropped two bombs.
First.. to get married!
The other, to send me to Russia.
It was my fault.
I should've kept mum.
I made a trip to Moscow to
attend a college seminar.
And what I saw there..
blew my mind.
Nikolai Vronsky, in fact had..
two Anna's.
One in India and
the other in Moscow.
I still blame myself for his death.
I shouldn't have
sent her those pictures.
Hi guys!
So great to be back.
Where's Anna?
She's at the market.
- But why? - For
her new wedding gown.
Goonga! Greatjob.
Lovely!
Feels so good.
The late Major..
her first husband.
Very brave, sir!
He was eaten by a panther,
wasn't he?
Shut up Goonga!
What did he say?
He says we pushed the Major down..
and then the panther ate him.
Don't believe him, sir.
He is a big liar.
Husband number two, Jimmy.
Very good song, sir!
Goonga, shut the hell up.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because he too, had a mother.
No, not at all.
Don't believe them,
they are just lying!
They say, that we gave
him an overdose of heroin..
then we dragged him to the cemetery.
Husband number three..
Wasiullah Khan a.k. a The Traveller!
We dug his grave in the snow..
and buried him alive.
Good sense of humour guys!
Where is Anna?
Anna is over here!
Look!
Anna's here!
And that is you..
Nikolai Vronsky!
My husband number four..
with his wife number two.
Cheers to that!
Four, four..
Where the hell did
you get this from?
R. A. W.
I'm asking you, who gave it to you!
R. A. W..
Anna, I was on a mission,
we were following a CIA man.
It's part of my job.
- It's part of my job,
you understand? - What!
To have a wife in every country?
A wife in every country!
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Give it to me, it's mine.
Just give it to me.
Run away! Run fast..
He ran away!
It's a mad house!
It's a mad house, you know!
You're crazy!
Come on, honey.
Come on, listen to me.
She is not my wife.
She is my colleague..
.. an agent.
And you.. a double agent!
Believe me.. we were just
acting like husband and wife.
I know you can play
a very good husband!
But to play such a great daddy.
No chance!
You're so wrong, Anna.
You're so wrong.
Always!
I'll quit the job, honey.
And I'll be back for you.
Forever!
My love for you is eternal.
Come on, you've been called.
Sir!
Have a seat, please.
How're you doing, Madame?
- It's you.. - Yes,
it's me.. Keemat.
Inspector Keemat Lal!
Officer Keemat Lal,
Intelligence Bureau.
This time, you're in real trouble.
- Look, Mr. Keemat..
-No 'Mr.' please..
Just Keemat.
I've gone through all your reports.
The local police is
convinced about your involvement.
According to them it's a
clear cut case of murder.
But the case is sensitive.
The Ministry of external affairs,
Russian embassy, are all involved..
You are an intelligent woman.
But, this time..
there is a certain item missing
from your husband's belongings.
If only I could get
my hands on that..
you get it?
Trust me.
That's it! Just
leave the rest to me.
Great!
By the way, what are you
doing this evening? Must be busy.
I need to inspect
the scene of the crime.
Maybe, some other time then..
Do you prefer
vegetarian or non vegetarian?
Don't bother..
non vegetarian.
And what would you prefer to drink?
Nothing in particular..
What do you prefer?
Anything but vodka.
You're going to get
me killed, Madame.
Sorry.. Sunaina.
Wow!
I think I've had a
bit too much to drink.
Never mind..
you'll sweat it out.
Where?
At the scene of the crime.
It is pretty deep.
In the dark anyone
could miss his step.
It was a full moon night.
Mind you, he didn't slip.
He climbed down..
on his own.
Must've been slippery
because of the rain..
.. and moss.
The rain?
In this season?
A lot of accidents can
happen when one is drunk.
He had quit drinking.
Alcohol!
How do I..
What should I say?
Forget about it.
Sorry?
Madame!
Darkness!
Pitch black!
Raining..
cats and dogs!
And..
the white man slipped.
Died!
Reached hell. The
bastard deserved it!
Madame!
I'll never forget this favour.
'Pure satisfaction.'
Like I've bathed a hundred
times in the holy waters.
No need to worry anymore.
If you ever come to Delhi..
I'd like to return the favour.
Should I go?
Yes!
Keemat left, only to return sooner.
He definitely reached Delhi..
but left his heart behind.
He'd come back for it everytime..
but always managed
to leave it behind.
Come Madame.
Come.
But Keemat kept on coming.
Saheb was left with no other option.
His quest for 'pure
satisfaction' knew no end.
I confessed to my wife.
Why?
I wanted a divorce.
And I got it too!
Here, look!
I can't live without you anymore.
I'd rather die.
I will die.
I swear on the Lord himself!
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son..
..and of the Holy Spirit, Amen.
Since it is your intention
to enter into marriage..
join your right hands and
declare your consent..
..before God and his church.
I Keemat Lal, take you Susanna
Anna Marie Johannes, to be my wife.
I promise to be true to
you in good times and in bad,
in sickness and in health.
I will love you and honour you,
all the days of my life,
till death do us apart.
I Susanna Anna Marie Johannes, take
you Keemat Lal to be my husband.
I promise to be true to
you in good times and in bad,
in sickness and in health.
I will love you and honour you.
.. all the days of my life,
till death do us apart.
Oh my God. There was
poison in the Viagra bottle?
The bottle contained Viagra pills.
What was it then?
Overdose?
Leading to a massive heart attack.
Very unfortunate!
Terrible accident!
Accident? She killed him.
And you knew it.
How would I know?
Of course, you wouldn't.
You were blinded by her love.
Some years later, I
returned from Russia, a Doctor.
But Saheb had
turned into 'a patient.'
My.. my.
Look at you!
What has the world
done to my little bunny!
Happy New Year, Saheb
What are you looking for?
I know there's one..
hiding somewhere.
I just can't seem to find
the rascal, when I want.
White hair?
Don't say it aloud.
It's a bad omen.
Here it is.
Show it. Let me see!
Fetch the scissors..
there on the record.
Snip it at the root.
See..
how much I need you.
Right there.. put it in the box.
I hate New Year's Eve.
When did you see me last?
It's been two years.
Do I look any different?
You've become a
little more beautiful.
I haven't changed at all?
Sure?
You've grown up to be shy.
Please don't, Saheb
Why not?
It's my
responsibility to educate you.
The delicate thread
between us had snapped.
That was the last time,
I ever saw her.
The next morning..
I took Goonga along
and left her forever.
The secondary post mortem reports,
and facial superimpositions..
as well as the PCR tests,
clearly indicate that..
the samples match.
Hence, it is proven that..
she is dead.
Thank God!
No one to fear, and no
favours to be returned.
You still miss her, right?
No.
Liar.
Get some sleep. It's pretty late.
It's an early morning flight
and you need to be in time..
..for security check.
And just don't let me
catch you dreaming about her.
Hello!
Yes, can I speak to Mr.
Arun Kumar, please?
Sorry?
No, can you check again, please?
He should have arrived last night,
with the Criminal Forensics Group.
Yeah.
Okay.. no, thanks.
Come on, Nandi. Get a grip.
It'll be fine. I have a
friend working at Vodafone.
We'll find out right now,
details about his last call.
Please calm down.
Here, have some water.
Mama.. mama.. it's daddy!
I told him you are very angry.
Hand me the phone.
Hello.. hello Arun.
Arun can you hear me.. hello!
Hello.. Arun.
Can you hear me? Hello!
Hello.
Hi Nandini.. how are you?
Where the fuck are you?
I tried calling you a hundred times.
There is no conference in Delhi.
Arun!
Say something for God's
sake Arun. Where are you?
Nandini, I'm fine wherever I am.
I'll be back in a day or two.
Arun, why?
For what?
Is there someone else in your life?
I can't believe, you
would betray me for anyone.
But there is someone.
Is she alive?
Arun?
Is Susanna alive?
I feel such comfort,
just by looking at you.
It all comes down
to love, sweetheart!
Do you need more
time to think over it?
No. I've already made my decision.
Alright then.
See you in the church at 11.
I've repaid your favours, Saheb
Your Saheb is no more..
sugar.
I kept looking for reasons
to live, after you were gone.
And one day, I heard
about your wedding.
What better reason
could I have waited for..
to end my life.
Asshole.. I almost ran into you.
The phone and car,
are both out of order.
My mistress needs to
get to the hospital.
Please, sir, for God's sake.
Please help, sir. Please!
Otherwise my mistress will die.
I was desperate to finally
rest in the arms of Jesus.
Looks like Jesus changed his mind.
Last minute hitch.
Maybe in guilt, he sent me an angel.
I was dead in my head.
But when I woke up,
felt a little strange..
a pair of spectacles on God's nose?
You are..
Tarafdar.
Dr. Modhushudhon Tarafdar.
Who slowly became the
big brother of the house.
He was considered some
kind of Miracle Doctor.
A strange concoction of allopathy,
naturopathy..
.. ayurveda and spirituality.
Ridiculous!
This mushroom is
called Jack O' Lantern.
It has a number of uses.
Very useful mushroom.
A bit could cure,
too much could kill.
There is plenty of evil all around.
Understand?
And even plenty is
never really enough..
it's always scarce.
But for the one who
survives even in scarcity..
nothing seems scarce.
Less, more.. more, less..
that's life.
So would you prefer
less or more in your soup?
For a healer like him, I was
willing to remain ill all my life.
And I would've but Modhu promised,
he wouldn't go back to Calcutta.
Marriage wasn't on my mind.
But Modhu wanted me to
be the heir to his wealth.
He was afraid that if he were
to leave this world before me..
then his ex-wife and
daughter would harass me.
My life was grounded..
but I was flying.
Modhu.. da.
What would I do without you!
Nothing!
- Come back fast. - Bye bye.
Khan..
what happened to the lights?
Khan.. Maggie aunty!
There's a robber upstairs.
And he has a knife.
Be careful!
News is just in that in
shootout at the Taj hotel..
NSE Major Sandeep
Unnikrishnan has been killed.
At the Trident
Oberoi and Nariman House..
Don't worry!
Everything will be fine, come..
come.
Modhu.
- Thank you. - Let me see?
Nice.
I was destined to be
with all the wrong men.
At first I was completely shattered!
But slowly I began to fear him.
For the first time, it was
my life that was in danger.
Look what I cooked
especially for you.
Your favourite!
Mushroom Veloute.
Susie!
Ghalib.. in the kitchen.
Yellow one, if taken in
large quantity is fatal..
.. but if you take
it in small quantity..
it produces hallucinations.
You know, what they call,
magic mushroom.
And this..
How can you think such a thing?
Have you lost it?
I saved your life.
Don't you remember?
Susanna..
What are you doing?
What is this, Susanna?
Susanna look..
This is a big misunderstanding,
Susanna.
Please.. this is a..
This is a big misunderstanding,
Susanna. And, even if it isn't..
what is the proof?
What are you doing?
Susanna, please don't do this.
Please, darling,
please listen to me.
Su.. Sus..
Susanna..
It's your turn.
Susanna.. I needed the money.
I really needed it.
I lost a lot of money in business.
I went bloody bankrupt, Susanna.
Oh God!
Susanna..
Susanna, I loved you, Susanna.
Susanna.. I.. I really loved you.
I truly love you Susanna,
believe me.
Oh God!
I wasn't even destined
for a peaceful death.
I had forgotten all the bullets,
next to Tarafdar's body.
Sleeping pills had failed once..
and I didn't want
to hang on a noose.
Jesus!
Susie!
Oh my Jesus..
I'd lost respect for myself.
I was shattered.
For a professional swimmer
drowning isn't an option.
I was punishing
myself for my cowardice.
A new death every moment.
And then I found out..
I was dead for the rest of world.
I couldn't let
Maggie's sacrifice go in vain.
She forced me to take
on life, one last time.
Of course, you were
forced into everything..
into marriage, into murders!
Did you ever stop to wonder,
why you committed all those sins?
For whom?
For my heart.
Your heart.. great!
My heart.
The heart..
For the sake of your heart..
you sent six people to their..
final abode before their time.
You won't understand, sugar.
Here's a little fact.
Every single wife..
has at least once in
her life entertained..
the thought of
getting rid of her husband.
Why don't you ask your wife?
I'm sure she's thought
of at least one way..
to murder you.
Any idea why you've survived?
A child!
A child makes..
the husband more acceptable.
That's the reason why
you never had a child!
You fulfilled that desire of mine.
Never have I shared
our love with anyone..
nor will I ever in the future.
In the future?
Now you won't find a
sacrificial lamb, Saheb.
Your beauty..
You've become a little scary.
Scary.. scary, scary!
He has accepted me
for the person I am..
with all my sins and
virtues and this scary..
scary face of mine.
Who?
My seventh husband.
I feel like getting
married again, you know.
For a change!
For a change?
There's a beautiful church,
in the old city.
Will you come?
Tomorrow morning. Eleven o'clock.
I won't let you take
another life, Saheb.
Hey sugar!
You won't be able to save him.
He has already
sacrificed himself.. for love.
He is dead.
And this time..
I am going to drink his blood.
The world, the
universe and its radiance..
aren't enough to satisfy my soul.
This peace, this joy, can be
attained, only through Jesus Christ.
Who is very dear to me.
The Lord of the Universe.
I, Sister Anna..
in the presence of Mother Mary..
solemnly vow to Lord Jesus that..
from now on I belong to Him alone.
From today he is my only master..
my spouse.
There is not a soul in sight now
Come, acknowledge me now, at least
Not a soul stirs this moment
Come, embrace me in your fold
Embrace me just this once
Then take me along
Hope there is no
misery on the other side
Jesus
You hear the tolling
of the church bells
Jesus
Yet all you choose
is to keep your quiet
Jesus
How do you pick who amongst
us is worthy of your grace
Jesus
You hear the tolling
of the church bells
Jesus
Yet all you choose
is to keep your quiet
Jesus
I want to confess my sins, Father!
My seven sins.
Arun.. Arun!
Stop the car! Stop it fast.
Arun! Arun!
I hate you, I hate you.
I'm fine, Nandini.
I told you I'll come back soon.
You lied to me!
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Did you say anything to the police?
I haven't told them the truth yet.
Or you'd be in jail for
the rest of your life.
If you ever..
try to see her again..
then I swear I'll kill you.
Never.
Ever.
She's dead.
Forever.
- Promise? - Promise.
What happened to your specs?
Someone cast an evil eye.