The thing that is yours if someone
will not give you
then steal it
yes KK I'm going for meeting
in life we have to try
your company's best copyrighters
have worked on this campaign
I have worked on it myself
what do you think what I'm
looking now?
This committee head has come
you are not going to take back
your case?
These files are ready for delhi,
courier them
who thought I will see this day?
I'm working here since 10 years
you all know me very well
do you think I will sexually
harrassment anyone?
Have you heard like this about me?
You have come from outside and you
are social worker too
maya luthra hai filed official
complaint against you
you have to give answer
I never needed to do this
nor I will need to do this
if this is fake then why maya will
do serious alligations against you?
Ofcourse he will say I'm lying
I dont know he needs me or not
I will very bad from inside
like the way peon look at me
we have to know from where
it started?
First of all we will thank
ourselves
I want to thank 1 important person
I forget to thank you
I have bring something for you
we have to celebrate
I dont know but you are expert
so you tell
I dont know about it you are looking
beautiful in green saree
we work here for 20 hours and
we sell condoms
if we dont do fun then it will
be a bad environment
I ignored it because we were friends
she is talking about trust
because of me she is in this
company
you are falling by yourself
my campaign was bad
your friends might like it but you
did not concentrate on product
because I dont work for you
she had willing to do
she only needed direction and focus
do you know where is rahul verma?
I'm selling children's tooth paste
then it must be childish
they will throw your campaign
you are teaching me to handle clients
we were thinking its children tooth paste
then we should think childish
these days you watch so many ads
which one you remember?
Because its different
if this campaign is not sucessful then
we will return your money
to win the world
he thaught me everything
I'm sitting infront of you
who got benefit in this relationship
you all knows
she showed me all her campaign
we have to change our all campaign
we have to show them different india
in saharan poor who will buy
this motor cycle?
Son goes with father to show room
we just have to go our place
mother will also have big part
mother says son has grown up
its not like it was just a
sexual relation for rahul
they were shooting in shimla and
he reached maya's house
you have come to meet me or
want to introduce rahul?
He also likes me
he is nice but he will not marry you
he is a very good copyrighter
what he said wrong?
You have come to gift rahul mangoes?
What happen?
A model has come to my house?
What you belong to me?
I want to go delhi
how delhi comes here?
Lets talk tomorrow
I want to go delhi
do you know what people
talk about me?
People will say because they
dont have to do anything
you will call KK
because there is no future there
you stop thinking about my future
may be maya has filed case to take
revenge from rahul
you got alot of benefits because
of this relationship
if I had to used him then why
did I left?
If a person ends relationship
then people say wow
you were not happy
when she went with that guy
I knew what will happen
they want to trap you
we cannot tell anyone
you told me you went to new york
for work
I wanted to see she will tell me or not
you must be very angry on her
you ask this from anyone in agency
rahul was unhappy from maya's
success?
He always supportjuniors
its a big announcement gonna happen
you are not ready for it
I'm accepting it because I deserve this
he was handling them since many years
and they took them from him
her behaviour is changed
you have 1 month notice,
find anotherjob
1 day unexpected thing happened
may I know why?
They dont know how to work.
How much chances I give them?
You cannot fire people
ok I transfer them banglore.
You are fighting infront of everyone
may be we dont have time for
your campagne
by small mistake you will lose
big money
why you do everything alone?
You are angry
today I will understand
what are you doing here?
Whatever I heard about maya and
rahul is true?
If i was not here then even john
would not appoint you
she has also come here
there is lots of difference came
between you
before me rahul was doing this
everytime he has to go somewhere
suddenly rahul was disappeared
i could not wait and I went
to his cabin
office is closed
there is 1 thing,
you forget to pack condoms
I have a big meeting with their CEO
I'm going to my home, my friends are coming,
you also come there
you think what is more important
i thought you have gone
i have come here for work
tell them you are working on new
campaign
i told you, you are not ready for
this
your career that I made
what are you doing?
I lost that account
I introduced her
she even dont know how to speall channel.
Why she used that perfume when she came?
You know clients never go
what do you want?
Where is campaign?
If has files. If you think I will write
campaign then its not my job
why you called a female colleague
at your house?
We often got late at work
then we go to my house
if you were feeling this they why
you did not complaint about it?
Thats our problem
its all your mistake
you were also in that room
I just want to say I tried my best and
I did not know its just a beginning
someone give you good shampoo
you think house wives behaves like this?
Why you were staring at me?
Why you are doing this?
I was working on presentation on so many days
and they give it so someone else
ok I will pick you up from airport
7 pm meeting is fixed
because one of my meeting
is rescheduled
what he is doing here?
Case is getting complicate so we
thought to discuss face to face
they are so many cars which
are cheaper and better
cars can work on 1 thing,
that is celebrity endorsement
yes I was angry but why I was angry she
did not tell you
I reached there
show me your campagne
I have to make this car number 1,
how you will make it?
This car dont have a single feature which
our consumer will like
may be we can sell this car but
this wont happen
why you did not tell this?
Yes he said this on airport
that you did with me in the room
bollywood celebrity idea was mine
how did you present it
without my permission?
You have forgotten I'm CEO of
this company
sometimes its good to be bad
did i tell you to change rules
of relationship?
So what do you want to say?
If i sleep with you then everything will be fine
did you say this?
You did not do anything like this
if i sleep with you then everything will be fine
you did not misbehave me?
I came to kill you?
What did you say?
Do you know how much I worked hard?
I leave this because one guy
has a problem from my success
you will withdraw this case
what you were saying? Only 3 women are
national creative director in india?
I'm going to files sexual harrassment
complaint against your CEO
rahul will not leave her
you have asked so many questions
to me
when we were having affair
did she complaint?
When she was getting promotions
If i got into this case then
i will lose my job
i cannot tolerate more insult
you go to bangkok and take
some massage
we will talk about it later
maya's blame are wrong
rahul cannot do this
they both are right at their places
I'm confused.
I cannot decide
you can do court case or they will
compensate you to take back case
she will not getjob
how you are feeling now?
Do you know what they will
do with you?
You want to win?
You cannot fire people
I met with a person who can
do anything with you all
teacher punished me to write 1000 times
on board i will not do this again
then i left it
i asked myself I'm doing wrong?
You all know it
you must be happy
i did everything to save my job
so what you care?
What you did with john?
He was talking about new york office
you allowed them to use you
if you care then you would not
allow me to go delhi
i told you dont go to delhi
you said there is no future there
whatever you did was good?
You came with john to
take my job?
I was in new york,
we met there
he came behind me
i came back for you
i thought you will be happy
and you will start loving me
what you did with john?
Is it anything possible between us?
You better ask yourself
this email is my resignation letter
i tell you why I'm going?
My father said it anyone proved you wrong
then always be with him
then i must have to know how it happened?
I'm leaving this agency by
making my dignity