Her age is 22.
You all are liars
You all will die
Whole house will drown
stop watching cinema in
black glasses
she has all the good things which
must have in a good wife
she is well cooked and
well mannered
whole day busy in pray
is this a wedding ad?
who idiot write this?
me
today's generation,
today's style
now see how smart and rich
boys will come to this house
1st time someone's name from this
house has published on newspaper
you did not find any other place?
move this dust bin from this place
did we give any home delivery order?
today we have 2 good news
we have found our dust bin
what are you doing?
give me breakfast
l dont know when l will
getjob
now you will only go to your
husband's house
l cannot marry in this house
near dust bin
what address you will tell
to people?
if you will cross the trash then
you will die from smoke
girl's father smoke 4 ciggarettes
in 1 time
her uncle cannot tolerate
pain of dogs
he finds dogs and take
them to home
in this country there is no place for
dogs and for people who love dogs
l will marry and run away from this
mental hospital
she is very beautiful and smart.
why you will marry to sharp shooter?
what a face and eyes you have
family members are mad but
girl is beautiful
they are coming to house at
6 PM and 9 PM
you have sold my tickets
in black
what are you doing?
why dont you throw all phones?
all these phones came for repairing
in 1983 and still they are here
say sorry to these dogs
do you want powder?
what do you think?
l think alot but now l think
you give me this job
yellow color
if you buy scooter then
what will be its color?
which is your favorite color?
go upstairs
someone is waiting for
you there
what was that?
l could not go to bollywood dance
class, thats why l was doing reharsal
l dont know why girls leave
this job
what will be my work?
you will tell me my work?
l know how to operate computer
why there are old
computers here?
tell me my work
you just come, still there is 1 month
remaining in college opening
my neighbour works in
censor board
you tell me my work.
l dont wanna watch unreleased movies
there is so much drama in my life
what are you doing?
so what l cant touch him.
l can see him
this job is very important for me
l want to earn money from this job
l want to buy freedom from
that money
where l read books and listen to
songs
l'm scared it will be in
2 to 3 days
today we gave ad in newspaper.
from today boys will come to see me
marriage should be after love
they dont allow me to live in reality
and dont allow me to see any dreams
there l dance and sing,
l live very happy there
dont interupt me
there is someone in my life
when l love him
and say lets run and marry
so that police will not find us
its just a small dream l have
and then fight with society people
from tonight l will fight with
truth
you will eat your fingers
will you also do my facial
after marriage?
your daughter will live happy
in our small family
sir's water is finished
go jumbo and come back fast
why he took your water bag?
lets go l'm very hungry
then l also have to dance
stop doing office work
you have already become dark and
you also cant do important work
dont know how to cook food
and doing computer work
is it necessary to smoke
while eating?
l dont like any of these boys
stop this program
from where you bring these
cartoons?
do you get a proposal from
any rich family?
he gave me yellow flower
in my dream
he was very boring
he was very fair and l dont like
people who wear vest
so you check if boy is wearning
vest or not?
l was expecting there phone
when they are coming or we
go to their house?
this relation cannot happen,
its out of budget
you do lots of work
dont increase work standard
it will be difficult for girls
l told you about my dreams
principle sir has called some details
what record he want to see?
he was a son of a rich father
what are you saying?
what will happen with internship?
his father died from his
wine credit
you were talking to them
day before yesterday?
what you know about them?
l have heard if they dont drink then
they would not have bright career
there are 2 chocolates on table,
1 is to open mouth
surya takes drugs
what do you know about drugs?
to go from this world to another world
thats why surya can see those things
which we cannot
this drugs news is fake
jumbo comes on your table
since 2 years surya was getting
gold medal
his painting also goes to
delhi painting exhibition
thats why he is here
l need your help
my cute girl
how to say l like white people
l can do this
if sleep come then dreams dont come
if dreams dont come then
dont need to sleep
rich boys take in parties
before food
drugs and cocaine is same
smell comes from body after
taking drugs
there is a general knowledge
contest
where is drug available in your city?
there is bridge near lake,
1 man daily stands there
its ok but what you will
do in future?
this my work. how l make big
house for dogs
in start i will be proprietor
then 1 day we will issue
public shares for our company
is this the same person?
if there is a single lake in jungle then
all animals come to this lake
now l'm also interested in these animals
go to that man and take
Rs 300 drugs
have you gone mad?
l just want to smell it
you are a coward
what are you doing?
she is our menakshi
why are you standing?
sit down please
no need to be formal
she has done computer course
what are your hobbies?
l like to study.
l like boobs and novels
l dont like cooking but
l can make good food
what are your hobbies?
l like this book
l have read it only once
she likes music too
l want to marry her
no need of it
can l talk to your daughter?
yes sure.
now this house is yours
l just said that l want to marry you
do you like me?
they did not ask you
its not good to go in room
without knocking
so good sarees in half price
l dont want your saree
what we ladies have to do
to take care of house?
your father never try to find you
after dropping at orphan palace?
may god bless him wherever he is
l just have a son.
l dont know l will marry for him
have some coffee
what kind of daughter in law
you like?
my house is not like before
if they come out from college
then they become amir khan
our surya will become amir khan
i was waiting for you
i like that others also like
l'm old fashion in movies
l dont like fighting
we will watch their movies together
now l must have to watch
they never wear designer clothes?
they never do so much
songs and dancing
do you speak less all the time?
only l'm talking since morning
you are the 1st person who
ask me what do l want?
what you have done?
if l will not die with this then
l will come infront of train tomorrow
l will burn everything
you are getting engaged then
wedding
l need time to think about engagement
you just leave job
and do facial
that house is not yours now
but tomorrow it will be yours
now we are making double
bed for madhav and menakshi
until now madhav sleeps
on a single bed
why you did not tell me?
you sit and l change my clothes
l have taken out something for you
this office is closed
there is nothing here
i dont want to go any beauty parlor
go and take her to
beauty parlor
our house is looking like set
of hum aap ke hain kaun
in the evening madhav is coming
with his relatives
why you did not tell me?
please dont tell this to anyone
whenever he is near to me then...
he is very nice
l'm also nice so that
you will marry me?
you have find out everything
about him?
he has a flower garden
on his terrace
he has no girlfriend record
yes l have to do this
love someone and marry someone
for how much he sells painting?
what is his social circle?
if you see him becoming famous
then marry him
except 1 thing
where is menakshi?
l was busy in preparation
since morning
l want ciggarette
look at his office work dairy.
there are some contacts in it
l go and check with him
we have not come here
to eatjalebi
its happening 1st time with me
l can feel something
1 palmist told me your dream
man will meet you
its my father's factory
4 years ago he died and
now l run it
l spend night time here
my mother dont like l do painting
she wants me to go foreign
and do some job
l become happy when l do
painting
you like your work
my parents and small brother
now everyone wants to
throw me from house
l asked in college about you
l live alone and l dont
give any explanation
why you asked so many people?
you ask me
everything is ready
lets start engagement
where is menakshi?
you went to bring her
l understand
she will show her face after
engagement
she will also tell her name
after engagement
you will be very happy to know her
parents will give me 10 crore capital
l dont drink
l also dont drink
l ride on old bike on
empty roads
wherever l go you come
behind me, why?
since l came out from college you
came after me
l dont know why are you doing this?
then you said your parents wants
to throw you out from house
my mother wants a smart
daughter in law
who will be ready to go anywhere
how to say l like black people?
show us your face
where were you?
are you ok?
l told you menakshi will come fast
he is surya
l'm also engaged
is she drunk?
when you met naina?
l told you to watch those movies,
dont forget to watch them
dont forget that we are friends
l want to marry your daughter
l like surya
l will be happy with him
l want to be engaged with him
if you are happy then what
else we want?
l dont know its a dream or truth?
since morning what is happenning
is out of my mind
its not a dream,
its truth
come and give us
blessings