♪ Fixed & Synced by
bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick ♪
What is happen to this city?
Ashes here, smoke there.
Why are you so silent?
Why have smoke forced
down your throat?
Why tolerate?
Why banned?
Let's bring this
reckless act to an end.
Smoking is banned in
all public places.
And it is apply.
Don't smoke.
No let anyone do.
Smoking will cost you.
Your one seeks happiness.
But isn't has a very
high price to pay.
Smoking can cost
you your health.
And can also seriously affect the
health and welfare of those who endure.
Don't have them pay the
price for your smoking.
Smoking will cost you.
Ferdie has a candle
for every ailment.
He's the postmaster
of the village...
but no one here writes
or posts letters.
The man with the golden voice.
The only choir boy who refused
to stop singing in church...
even after he wasn't
a boy anymore.
Floating in a life inside his own
head, my best friend Ferdie...
who'll never have a
story to tell...
unless the story comes
looking for him
This is my home. This is
my village of Pocolim.
Hidden somewhere in Goa.
Don't try looking for it.
You won't find it.
Time passes in a
strange way here.
It stops when you stop...
and runs when you run.
Isn't that interesting?
I wonder what I wish
for everyday...
Maybe, wishing is a bad habit.
Like picking your nose and
wiping it under the table...
or eating too much spicy
Sorpotel in summer.
Yet, not a day passes
without a wish.
This is Rosalina,
my mother-in-law.
You know some peoples are just
want to take charge to everything.
Imagine a puppet-show,
as large as a village.
If Mai ever threw
away the strings...
life in Pocoli would
just crumble to a halt.
Happy feast.
Call me Mrs. Eucharistica.
Mrs. Eucharis... - Forget it.
So you're Maria's...
The one Maria's
sis-in-law spoke about.
You call this a bio-data.
Why oh why?
Why means what, aunty. - What?
What?
You just said 'Why means what'.
No, I mean you said... I said...
That's the problem
with you youngsters.
You just can't speak properly.
How why means what?
Idiot. Come on.
Now say fast, what you want.
Aunty Maria said you'll fix
me up with a nice girl.
Fair complexion
and full of life.
Does your aunty think
I'm a magician?
I'll go to the gym.
So what are you waiting for?
Christmas?
Whether it's a leaf on a tree
or a dog on the street...
no one can move an inch,
without Mai's permission.
If you mess with Mai,
it's best to leave town.
Except, in Pocolim
nobody leaves.
Angie.
Yes, Mai.
Did Nereus drink
his milk properly?
Can't you land on your feet?
Mai.
Have you noticed Nereus
keeps falling asleep...
at the strangest of times?
What's so strange about it?
He sleeps when he feels sleepy.
You know it's called Narcolepsy.
Where you keep falling asleep.
You leave Nereus alone.
He knows better than you
how to behave like a cat.
Next you'll be telling me
how much I should sleep?
Rosie and I have just
one thing in common.
Loneliness.
I don't know when
Rosie's husband died.
She never speaks of it.
And I never ask.
As for me, I was married
to Rosie's son Gabo.
Very handsome.
Every girl wanted to marry him.
That's what he thought.
I don't know if I was
in love with him...
but he was already very
much in love with himself.
And anyway... no one
ever said no to Gabo.
Our wedding was the
talk of the town.
From food and drinks,
all the arrangements...
were simply the best.
Rosie did everything.
Gabo was so happy that day...
that he couldn't imagine
life getting any better.
And for him, it didn't.
But life was looking
up for Rosie.
She now had an admirer.
A famous artist had
moved to Pocolim.
A magician with the paintbrush.
Every stroke of which...
earned him a standing
ovation from the art world.
They say that Don Pedro Cleto
Colaco has just one inspiration.
Women.
Big women.
I told you I'll set you up!
What are you doing here?
She's right here. Why
can't it be now?
She's busy.
You have to wait if you
want it done properly!
Wait for what?
The Second Coming?
You've been waiting
for 2000 years.
Any luck?
I can't talk right now.
Please leave.
Rumor has it, he's only
looking for only one thing...
his last inspiration.
And this... is Savio.
We were friends until
I broke his heart.
He just came back home...
after 6 years.
To no family.
Probably searching for some
imagined family treasure...
in this empty house, all alone.
He's a broken man.
And I did the breaking.
Savio, Gabo and I
grew up together.
Those two were inseparable...
but also fiercely competitive.
So when I told Savio that
I am marrying Gabo...
without saying a word,
he left Pocolim.
He returned after making
his fortune in Mumbai...
for his father's
memorial service.
There was no point
in coming earlier.
Rosalina had taken
care of everything.
Jesus Christ, what the...
Who is this?
You didn't recognize him?
It's your father.
But this was a
black-and-white photograph.
It was fully gone.
You couldn't even take
a good picture of him.
That's my fault too?
But why didn't you
use the original?
Look at him.
Are you talking about him?
Because he's dead.
Savio...
Savio, another word
from you and...
Hold on.
So this was also
my father's idea?
What did he say?
Paint my face pink.
Make me a clown.
This... this was Eddie's idea.
Who the hell is Eddie, Father?
Is he blind? Is he retarded?
Look, Savio... it's just a
little digital retouching.
BY Whom? A monkey?
Is Eddie a chimpanzee?
Is he a monkey?
No.
Ferdie.
I'm in the back side.
I think Savio Da Gama is back.
Return of the missing son.
Remember Savio?
What's this for?
This I'll light for my
broken heart Angie.
Hey, what happened?
Ferdie!
I knew it was you last night.
Continue like this, and...
everyone's going to think
that you're possessed.
Are you?
This is Assumption.
How can you even say that?
It's a mutton bill, Ferdie.
Stefanie Fernandes.
Fanny.
But why didn't you
post this letter?
I did.
It came back, last night.
After 46 years.
But you're in-charge
of the post...
so who gave it to you?
Ferdie, you proposed to her.
- Then what?
I asked her hand in marriage.
But she never replied because...
this letter was never
delivered to her.
You're damn angry...
46 years!
For 46 years I thought
she had rejected me.
What life is this?
Full lie I've lived.
Full lie I've lived, for something
that never even happened.
It's okay. - It's not okay.
Stefanie Fernandes was
and will always be...
the love of my life...
and she never even knew.
So why didn't you tell her?
I thought she'd say know.
But, if you don't ask...
how will you know what
her answer would be?
After waiting so long...
I wish I had kept waiting.
You've been crying?
None of your business.
This is Pocolim, Ferdie.
Out here, everyone's business
is everyone else's business.
Does it work?
None of your business.
It's funny.
How you can cry underwater?
Angie. Angie.
You're crying? - Yes, Mai.
But I think there's
a robber outside.
What are you doing?
Looking for the robber, Mai.
Are you mad or what?
You're making so much noise.
You'll scare him away.
Angie.
Go away.
- Who are you talking to?
The dogs.
These dogs. - They gone.
Come in.
They're gone.
I'll take care of their barking.
Mai...
They always trouble my Nereus.
Go and sleep.
- Lock the door properly.
Ferdie.
What happened? - Is she gone?
Yeah.
I had a dream.
What dream?
About Fanny.
Really?
And?
She was taking me to a church...
and she was saying
something to me.
And?
Then I drowned me in the dream.
And then? - Then what?
What happened to Fanny?
Oh she...
She was doing some...
Listen Ferdie, we
have to find Fanny.
No, no, no, I drowned.
I'm telling you I drowned.
Look at me Ferdinand.
Look at me.
Do you want to die
without telling Fanny...
that all your life,
you've loved only her?
No. - Then?
I don't want to die.
No, Ferdie.
No love story should be
left incomplete like this.
Savio Da Gama.
He?'-
It's been 6 years, huh?
Looking good.
What's this?
My side-door neighbor brought
us some Tang, from Dubai.
Side-door.
Six years Savvy, nobody
knows anything about you.
Whether you're alive, or dead...
or married?
You know Gabo died that day.
Your train must have been
leaving from Goa at that time.
You didn't even attend his funeral.
Not even...
What was I supposed to
come back and do Angie?
Bring him back to life?
No letter, not even
a phone call...
For what?
My friend died.
Felt like Shit.
By the time I found out...
he was already gone.
So...
did you get married?
Looking good.
The car, looks nice.
Are you really selling it?
Do you want to buy it? - No.
It's for someone called 'SAL'.
So...
still pressing Rosie's feet?
Please, Savio, at
least I'm happy.
Like always.
So what's your problem?
You know there's a world
outside Pocolim, right?
Life isn't easy here, but we
make the most of it, okay?
Really?
What do I know about problems?
Anyway-
I feel like I'm asking a
stranger for a favor.
What favor?
I need the car.
This is no longer my car.
- Then whose is it?
That artist.
That Pedro?
How did this happen?
Lots of money coming your way.
Can't complain.
Stop pretending.
I've heard about your
big business in Mumbai.
Well, yeah!
Anyway, what do you
need the car for?
That stingy bugger won't
lend it to anyone.
You know that postmaster Ferdie?
He and I are going
on a short trip.
Running away with
the postmaster?
Yes... if the artist lends
me the car will you drive?
He won't give it
unless you bribe him.
Rosie. Rosie.
Mrs. Eucharistica, Mr. Colaco.
Of course.
I want to make a
painting of you...
for all the social
work that you do.
It will be shown in places
like Milan, New York, London.
I think it's a
wonderful idea, Mai.
No, no... I mean...
But, come on you have to.
Yes but...
- You go to the church every day.
Up and down. Up and down.
So much work you do.
You can at least do this much for yourself.
- It's God's work.
Can you see it, Madame Eucharistica?
- What?
Can you see yourself in
the painting, Madame?
Oh Rosie, it's my...
I mean, your future.
Can you see it please, now?
No. Not really.
I mean, sometimes I get a
little carried away, you see.
Don't worry.
Sometimes, Mai's also
in a different mood.
That's okay. But... - Nothing.
What you offered her was nice only.
- Yes, of course.
You must be busy these days
with your foreign trips?
Busy?
I don't have the time
to breathe, darling.
Oh...
Because we were
planning a road trip.
Who we? - Mai and me.
I thought you'll get a
chance, you know...
to know her better.
But it's okay. Next time.
Time is what I don't have.
It's alright. - No, no, no, no.
I'll adjust.
Everything happened
so fast that...
I'm sorry I didn't get a
chance to tell you earlier.
Anyway... I'll leave from Chapel
Point at 11 in the morning...
for a matter of
Christian charity.
I'm going to help Ferdie.
He needs my help more than
anyone else in the world.
Don Pedro has offered his
car for this journey and...
of course, he's coming along.
Sweet of him, isn't it?
He couldn't stop going on about
how he wishes paint you.
All he keeps talking about is...
capturing your elegance
and beauty on canvas.
So flattering, isn't it?
It started.
I'll just have to be careful
of our driver, Savio.
The way he looks at me
makes me uncomfortable.
But how will I stop him?
By looking at your photo.
I will stop myself from getting
drawn into temptation...
You've always taught me to put
other's needs before ours.
And now is the time to put
this into practice...
so the world will say
that Rosalina...
has taught her
daughter-in-law well!
What are you doing here?
There's a lady
coming on this trip.
You could've cleaned the car...
before bringing it here?
I hope the seats are clean.
Leather and sweat smell like
pigs' piss after a while.
This is rexine, you idiot.
You...
What did you say?
I said it's clean.
You...
She's here.
The beautiful Angelina.
The glow on your cheeks
puts the sun to shame.
And the Romeo of Romeos.
The Casanova of the Konkan.
You're an inspiration to lovers.
I salute you, sire.
And where's the
other lovely lady?
She'll be coming, soon.
I'll be right back.
I'm here only.
Why are you holding my hand?
Listen, before you
get furious...
let me tell you, this was
out of my control, okay.
Lies.
What did you expect me to say to him?
Don't come.
You tricked me into
driving this car.
What do you mean I tricked you?
This is his car, after all.
Listen, I just wanted to
get out this village.
Finally, I wanted to spend some time...
- I'm sorry.
I had to help Ferdie.
So you lied.
You know what, to hell with him.
And don't talk to me, just go.
You know, Savio...
sometimes, you need to make
an effort to find love.
Angie, this is why...
She's also coming along?!
Rosalina, the first
lady of Pocolim.
What a lovely day this is...
that comes with the
privilege of your company.
My humble car awaits.
Come. - Here.
Why do you drop everything?
Are you butter fingers?
It moved.
Of course it moved, it's a cat.
Don...
Madame.
What a lovely cat. Just
making a bit of noise.
Has it come to say
goodbye to us?
Will Nereus come along, Mai?
We need to discuss some
important things, young lady.
Look here.
Come.
How will I face my Gabo...
if I can't even protect
his wife's purity?
Proud of you. - Thank you, Mai.
And there's no one to
look after Nereus.
He'll be fine. He'll
stay with me.
You take care of him.
You okay?
What a lovely car, Don Pedro.
Yes, I thought so too when I
saw it for the first time.
Just needed a bit of repair.
Nothing much though.
Hey you, can you drive a
fine imported car like this?
Hey, it's you I'm talking to.
And good morning.
Your mother must have forgotten
to teach you manners.
It's okay, I'll teach you.
You're asking me if I can drive?
I mean... are you qualified?
It's a foreign car after all.
What?
The gears are different.
Can anyone here drive this car?
Since you know a lot about foreign
cars and their bloody gears?
I can't...
And since this is
Don Pedro's car...
and he doesn't know how
to drive, so who's left?
Huh, madam?
I don't trust this
hooligan's driving.
Everything should be alright.
God mess.
Okay Ferdinand...
Thank you.
Ferdie, we really don't need
to make this small talk.
Sorry.
There's something
strange on your face.
No... I mean.
Why are you speaking now?
Hey Ferdie, open the bottle.
He couldn't even get water?
Couldn't even do this much?
I keep doing work for
others all the time...
but no one cares.
I'm thirsty, one second.
Yuck! What is this?
What are you doing?
What?
What am I doing?
Yes, what are you doing?
How much longer will I
have to wait, god dammit?
What are you saying?
So tell me, Ferdie, how come no Mrs.
Ferdie all these years?
Oh...
Just like that.
There was no one else...
after Fanny.
She is for real, right?
Romeo without a Juliet.
Sorry.
I want to put this cat inside.
Wipe your face.
He looks alive, doesn't he?
What?
Does anyone want to tell
Mai what just happened?
Exactly.
So we'll stop somewhere on the
way and say a prayer for Nereus.
You mean, she'll
wake up and see...
that Nereus passed
away in his sleep?
Yeah.
See... see.
Fanny's house.
Happy?
Come.
This house is bigger
than your palace.
Pretty, no?
Pretty, like my Fanny.
This is it, sir.
It's your show from now.
Come on, you Romeo.
No more thinking.
Make or break.
Ferdie.
Hey...
Go get him.
Get him.
Ferdie. Ferdie.
Ferdie, wait up.
Ferdie.
Ferdie, wait. Wait.
What if...
What if she doesn't
recognize me?
Mad or what?
Who would forget a
personality like yours?
Yes, I haven't changed much.
I'm the same. - Yes.
So there's nothing
to worry about.
Yeah. Show her your
romantic side.
There are thorns everywhere.
Show. Show.
Ferdie. Hold this.
Stupid.
You should've got
some other flowers.
Why did you pluck roses?
- Savio said.
I look alright?
Excuse me, sir.
We're looking for
Stefanie Fernandes.
Of course, you are.
She's waiting for you.
You must come in, please.
Come, come.
Welcome to my home!
She married a foreigner? - No.
He's a bloody hippie.
Russian. I'll handle it.
What is he talking?
What do you want my friend?
An umbrella would be nice,
but we're looking for...
What's her name?
- Stefanie Fernandes.
This is her husband, he
wants to tell her that.
Not like that.
This morning,
Stefanie Fernandes...
runs away with my umbrella.
With your umbrella?
This morning?
You must all sit.
I come back.
Any pictures of Fanny?
I can't really tell.
My name is Vladimir llyanova.
But you can call me
Vladimir llyanova.
Both.
Hey you?
Why you have brought yellow
flowers to my house.
Don't you know it's bad luck?
They are for Fanny.
What is funny?
Fanny. - This is not funny.
Stefanie Fernandes, remember?
Sir, Stefanie
Fernandes your wife?
My wife...
My wife is in Russia, long dead.
And my mother...
Can I offer...
Why are you doing this to me?
Please take them outside.
Excuse me.
This man has come looking
for Stefanie Fernandes.
You know her, right?
Vladimir?
Vladamir.
My mother named me Vladimir.
- Sir.
You bought this house
from Stefanie Fernandes?
20 more years ago.
Wonderful lady.
She moved to Tivoli...
that is few hours on the
other side from here.
The government made
a lot of problems..
"About selling to a foreigner.
But... I had married an Indian.
So... I got lucky.
Lovely lady Stefanie Fernandes.
Just star-t the car
when I tell you.
Savio. - Yes.
Thanks.
For what?
I love her.
I really love her.
Hey, Savio.
Tell you a secret?
Yeah...
You know Albert and I
were shippies together.
Rosalina's husband, Albert.
I heard.
We sailed together
that last time...
just before he never came back.
So you were on the
ship when he died.
He didn't die.
He did not die. - What?
Just never came back.
Just wrote her a letter saying
he's never coming back.
Gave me to give her.
But... wasn't there
a big memorial?
Rosalina, the pregnant widow...
Husband buried at sea.
He found a girl in Madagascar.
Jumped ship, disappeared.
What I mean is why
tell such a big lie?
Of course.
Pride.
Her bloody pride.
That's why she hates
me, you know.
Because I am the
only one who knows.
Apart from her and Albert.
Now you know.
That explains her bitterness.
Promise you won't tell her.
Then why you told me?
Be nice to her.
Sometimes.
When I was small, I
used to be an angel...
in feasts.
Do you want to hear a song?
Okay then.
Either this car
doesn't use petrol...
or we need to get some
when we get to Tivoli.
You want to hear some songs
I wrote about Fanny?
No Ferdie, I would like to
know where that right turn is.
It'll come.
It'll come on the right.
Oh my little pussy.
Pussy. Pussy.
Pussy.
You're such an
animal lover, Pedro.
Madame.
I've never loved an
animal as much as this...
lively little fellow.
Give him to me, must be hungry.
No, no, no.
I assure you that
he's quite stuffed.
Come, my little baby.
Come, come, come.
That's it. On the right.
Stop. Stop the car.
Stop the car. - Why?
Stop the car.
Hello, everyone.
I just want you to say.
I could not have done
this without you all.
What man, now you're
giving a speech or what?
My Fanny's village
is just up ahead.
I hope my hear-t doesn't
burst with happiness.
When I meet Fanny...
I'll talk to her
only with my eyes.
Might be a blessing.
Why don't you do the
same for us, you idiot?
Talk with your eyes only.
Anyway... you all
made it possible.
Especially you, Angie.
My hear-t was like a bird...
that could not fly.
It would never be able to fly...
if it wasn't for you.
Thank you, Ferdinand.
Fernando. Fernando.
Fanny always used to
call me Fernando.
Not a bad speech.
You should have one ready
for Fanny if you see her.
Everybody ready?
Everyone ready?
Start the car. Start the car.
Faster. Faster.
Give me the map.
Why?
You idiot, we're in
bloody Karnataka.
Means what?
Means we've crossed
into another state.
What state?
A bloody mental state.
He's shouting.
Mad he's become or what?
And you... please explain.
When did I say I can read a map!
The days in which I
had to fall in love.
I spent all those days
writing letters to you.
O Fanny Re...
All the happiness's of my life.
Got killed as I was lost in the
thoughts of Your whereabouts.
O Fanny Re...
O my beloved!
Now what?
Now... now what? We've
run out of petrol.
O Fanny Re...
Savvy...
Savio.
Yeah, what?
What are you doing?
Getting that bloody
idiot out of my system.
I didn't sign up for this bullshit.
- Oh, sorry.
For what?
My fault, trusting that
fool to read a map.
It's like a chimpanzee
reading Shakespeare.
It's not that bad.
- Not that bad?
And that painter bullshitter!
Madame this. Madame that.
What Madame?!
She's just a fat old cow.
They are old people, Savvy...
and old people will
be old people.
You can't change that. - Right.
They get away with a lot
of shit, old people.
Good excuse.
If you stay alive long enough..
People eventually forget
that you were born stupid.
What's your problem?
You've more than most people do.
So why are you complaining all the time?
- One second.
What do I have?
20 dentures.
10 shins, 5 pants, 3
socks and 2 underwear.
That's all dear daddy left me.
Oh, did I forget to mention?
One bloody falling down house.
Well, I can't complain.
I never had any daddy,
dentures or house.
Oh, please, spare me your
little orphanage sob story.
Poor Angie, alone in this world.
You let her rule over you.
That's your choice.
Look, Angie, I'm sorry.
I really have nothing
against you.
And if anything,
you're the only one...
If it wasn't for you...
I would've killed
someone by now.
Listen...
maybe if we plan wisely..
We can do up the
house slowly-slowly.
Till then I'll come and
help you clean the house.
What?
There's no money
in Mumbai, Angie.
But the business?
- What business?
I was a bloody
waiter for 5 years.
Slept on the same
tables I served.
So you lied.
I'll still help you
clean the house.
For free.
Lomos Del Toro.
One of the finest brandies
known to man, Madame.
This is good.
You're classy.
Classy, Don Pedro.
Indeed, Madame.
I see that you have a fine palette
of a sailor on shore leave.
No doubt that you got
it from your husband.
Husband.
May his soul rest in peace.
You think he's watching?
Let him.
I mean why should he alone
have fun in heaven?
He had lots of fun, nonstop.
These sailors, dirty people.
No respect for their
wives at home.
But my Albert wasn't like that.
My Albert was very faithful.
If I were your
husband, Madame...
I wouldn't go away from
you even for a moment.
All lies. You men all lies.
If you don't go to
work, who'll earn?
Your father?
Of course.
How is the brandy, dear lady?
Call me Rosie no,
nobody else does.
Rosie.
Now the picture is perfect.
I used to miss you
in the beginning...
until I started enjoying
thinking about you.
About us.
You know I used to make
up my own stories.
About what could've happened if
things had gone differently.
If... life hadn't changed...
or you hadn't left Goa...
Mumbai wasn't easy.
Memories were all I had...
So it's a deal then?
What deal?
I want the old Savio back.
Same old...
Jesus Christ, what the
hell was that for?
You've gone mad or what, Savio?!
I've gone mad?
So what were you thinking?
I'm good for a little charity,
a little house-clean...
but a peck on the lips
and I've gone mad?
What am I thinking?
What are you thinking?
So what was all that
'we' stuff about?
We'll clean the house.
What was all that about?
We, Savio. You and I,
aren't we even friends now?
Friends?
Aren't you fed up of
this friends bullshit?
Back then we were friends,
now we're friends!
Why the hell did you
say yes to him...
when you knew you loved me more?
Why?
Just because he asked you first?
No, Savio.
Because you never asked.
Are you mad creeping
up like this?
I would've knocked
but there's no door.
You could have at least cleared
your throat or something...
My throat is not blocked.
- Okay.
I came to tell you all...
my decision.
Romeo of Pocolim is going
to make another speech.
Anyway, I want you
all to know...
that tomorrow morning I
am going for petrol.
The only reason I
am not going now...
is because I am
scared of the dark.
And I can't cure that overnight.
It is almost impossible...
to conquer the fear of
the dark in the day.
Too much light.
And also there's.
I am scared of snakes.
There are too many
snakes in Goa.
For the first time,
Ferdinand is thinking.
About somebody else
instead of himself.
I'm impressed.
Do whatever you like.
I'm not in a hurry to go home...
as long as she's by my side.
Your choice.
You stay here, go back...
Whatever.
I am going to look for Fanny.
Wait. Ferdie, come here.
Come, come.
Have some brandy.
There is no third glass, Madame.
Come. Sit, drink from my glass.
Come.
Listen, I don't want to fight.
Listen Angie, screw you.
What have you come back for?
I don't want your sympathy.
You think you're very tough...
to use whatever language you
choose to especially with a girl?
Girl?
- I'll smack your face, Savio.
I'm not scared of you
or your language...
or your stupid attitude.
Go away, I've nothing
to say to you.
That's always been the
problem with you.
You think something was there?
What did you think was there?
You and I were..
We were close, remember.
We were 18, Savio.
No, you were 18, I was 20.
Shit. I'm such an idiot.
Why didn't I just say it then?
You know, you're
worse than Ferdie.
He at least said it but
Fanny never heard.
But you... proud
Savio Da Gama...
couldn't say what
was in your heart.
No, Angie...
Now let me speak, okay.
The first time I was kissed
was on my wedding day.
And 15 minutes later my
husband choked and died..
On his own wedding cake.
It's not the chicken
bone as the story goes.
The bride and groom figurines on
the cake were made of plastic.
Not icing.
His mother was trying
to save money.
And her son was so drunk that.
By the time he realized it
was halfway down his throat.
That was my first and last
kiss and it was 6 years ago.
You think I did something
wrong by slapping you today?
Huh?
Is your ego hum?
Where does it hum?
You think after
waiting 6 years...
a girl would not like
it to be done properly?
No...
I mean yes.
So then finish what you started.
Sure about this, I mean..
I don't really...
No, I've had too much already.
You have.
Forget it.
Too much liquor is bad
for me, you know.
It affects my legs.
Gout?
No.
It makes them spread.
You remember the
old days, Ferdie?
Albert, you and me, we
used to have so much fun.
Ferdie.
Ferdie, thanks.
You always knew about
Albert and me.
That bastard.
I never asked you to... but
still you didn't tell.
Thanks for keeping my secret...
a secret.
Thanks Ferdie.
Angie.
Angie, you okay?
Would you like a cigarette?
Like a tradition afterwards.
Angie, really are you okay?
I am okay. Just...
lying and watching the stars.
Look here, I want to
make sure you're okay.
I am okay.
Talk to me, baby.
Despite what everyone says
about men wanting to...
turn around and fall
asleep after...
That's also a tradition?
I thought she's going
to come and check.
Who?
You were making bit of a sound.
What are you mumbling about?
Angie, you know who?
Again you're talking about Mai.
Why are we always
talking about Mai?
Don't be naive, Angie.
What are you going to
tell Rosie about us?
Mad or what?
Why will I tell her anything?
What do you mean?
This is a one-time
thing for you?
That's all this is?
I didn't say that.
I'm hoping there'll
be many more times...
and I'm hoping it will
get better also, no?
Better?
What do you mean better?
Is this the best it ever gets?
No... but... I mean..
So, better?
My sky. - What?
You're in the way of my sky.
Yeah, fine.
Hey!
Listen, if I had
not come to you...
you would still be sitting
here and sulking.
So let me do what I want no...
Better?
Somebody should go with Ferdie.
He won't know what to get.
You think he'll bring back
apple juice in a jerry can?
But what if he gets lost?
He got lost a long time ago.
Somebody's coming.
Bring back some apple juice.
Good morning. - Morning.
Someone should look
out for Ferdie.
Of course, you go.
You and M.F Hussain.
You look out for him...
while Hussain can
look at more of you.
Don't think I don't know what's
going on in your dirty mind.
My dirty mind?
Wait till he takes
out his paintbrush.
Then tell me dirty mind.
I don't want to talk to you.
The moment is at hand, my lady.
What are you going
to do with this?
With this brush I will
awaken the soul that...
exists within this
beautiful body.
And put colors on to it...
the world does not
have names for yet.
With each dab of paint...
I will give your
beautiful soul..
A new skin.
God will wish he had left the
creation of women to Pedro.
Angie, I am sorry.
Sorry for being such an idiot.
I don't know much
about these things.
And I don't smoke.
But maybe if I did...
I would be the one who would want
to roll over and smoke a cigarette.
After we make love.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Put your hands up!
And stay there!
Madame Eucharistica.
Drop the cloth a little
off the other shoulder.
I am not so sure. - Drop it.
This is an, my dear.
No compromises.
Don Pedro, I'm not
comfortable wearing this...
I assure you, Madame.
This sheet is not
even in my painting.
So, stay like this.
Yes, that's better.
Where the hell are those two?
Don Pedro is painting
a portrait of Mai.
And she agreed?
It's for the church.
Church?
You have not seen the
famous Don Pedro's work...
Church.
This is beautiful.
Seldom have I been so wrong...
in recognizing someone.
How can somebody so
magnificent to look at.
Be so completely
empty from the inside?
Where had your mind been...
while your body was
working its magic...
filling itself out, becoming a
deadly lure for the artist.
You know the hardest pan of
finishing this painting, Madame?
Your eyes.
Where is your soul?
I do not see.
So...
I had to make it up.
It's like making love to you
and thinking of another.
You're free to go.
I am done with you.
Dear Angie, madam Rosalina,
Don Pedro and Savio...
sorry for dragging
you all into this.
But I needed you all
to help me start.
I don't expect you to
understand my love for Fanny.
I understand it hardly.
What I understand is this.
You won't find
anything by waiting...
but only by searching.
Angie, you're the
daughter I never had.
And you're the wife I
hope Fanny will be.
And I wish my mother
had been like you.
Whoever you touch is the
luckiest bugger in the world.
Even if they don't know it then.
Don Pedro, I'm sure
you'll make...
"the lovely madam Rosalina
famous in your painting.
I hope each one of you fulfils
something in your life.
Will I see you again?
Maybe, maybe not.
I don't know.
Good. Now we can go back.
I guess it's his own
journey from here on.
I mean...
we were meant to be with
him only up till here.
Come.
Wait. - It's time to go home.
What do you mean by going home?
How can we go without Ferdie?
Have you all gone mad?
Let go.
And you... you don't care
about anybody else..
"But yourself. - Mai...
You're selfish, you selfish...
Good for nothing.
That's what you are.
It should've been you that day.
Not my Gabo.
Gabo shouldn't have died.
Leave me, Angie.
Do you know why he married her?
Do you know?
Because he always
wanted what you wanted.
God takes away the good and
leaves behind the trash.
My Gabo should've lived..
You should've died.
- This is not Pocolim, okay.
This isn't your house.
Or your daddy's village.
And I am selfish?
I am selfish? - Yes.
All your life you've
been strutting around...
parading your false pride!
And I am selfish?
Shut up.
- I'll show you who's bloody selfish, wait.
Where are you going?
Mai. - Where are you
going now, you coward.
Don't you do anything to my cat.
Cat. Your bloody precious cat.
Here.
Your bloody cat has been
dead this whole time.
As dead as your bloody son.
Have you fed it once?
Looked after it once?
Are we your pop's servants
to take care of it...
while you pose
around like a model?
And now suddenly Ferdie
this, Ferdie that.
All your life you treat
him like shit...
and now suddenly it's Ferdie.
Ferdie my ass!
Done with this shit.
Hey, you found daddy's gun.
- Let me die.
Found his gun..
- Let me die. Let me die.
You found his gun.
Thank you so much
for finding it.
Do you know how much it's worth?
How much?
What are you doing?
We're going back? - What?
I don't know what
I was thinking.
We'll have to go
back for Ferdie.
For Ferdie?
I am the one who
slipped the letter..
Under his door that night.
What?
Found it when I was going
through daddy's old stuff.
Like everything else in life..
Daddy must have messed up again.
Yes, now I remember.
Jesus Christ, you think
even this is about you?!
It's about your
daddy, you idiot.
Loyolla was the
postmaster that time.
Daddy was surely a
man of many talents.
Ferdie! Ferdie! Ferdie!
Ferdie! - Ferdie!
Ferdie!
Stop the car.
- Are you mad, stop the car!
Shit the bloody car's brakes are failed!
- Stop the car.
Stop the car, Savio.
The brakes have failed!!
Give it to me. - Stop the car.
Mad woman, leave the steering.
Stop.
- Leave the steering, you fat cow.
Give me the steering.
- Stop her, Angie.
Savio..
I don't want to die.
You stupid fat cow.
Bloody two minutes back you
wanted to kill yourself.
Now you don't want to die.
Are you mad?
Stop the car. Stop the car. Savio, please.
- Leave.
Mai!
It's okay.
Come, come.
Where are we?
We are okay.
Idiot.
Move.
I nearly died.
So did we.
Hey...
where's Don Pedro?
I saw that bloody
selfish bastard.
He jumped off to save himself.
- No.
I asked for help and he
slapped my hand away.
I saw that, Mai. - You're okay?
Don Pedro.
Hey“
Go, go, run you selfish
coward bastard.
Go!
Great.
Even after reaching,
we can't reach.
Let's find out where she lives?
Oh, my God!
Fanny!
Which one?
Where?
Come on, Ferdie, go for it.
You've waited your
entire life for this.
No, l... l think I'll wait only.
Ferdie. Hey, Ferdie.
Go on.
You sure?
Ferdie, wait.
Fanny.
It's me, Ferdie.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, I am sorry.
I thought you were Fanny.
Who the hell is Fanny?
Fanny. Stefanie Fernandes.
Just get away.
Stefanie is my mother.
Where is she?
No...
It can't be.
No.
Are you...
You're sure it is her?
Means what?
She doesn't look like..
She's wearing a wedding dress.
Shouldn't she be..
- Recently married, no?
I knew it.
My Fanny waited for
me all these years.
And now she got married.
Fourth time...
What did you say your name was?
- Ferdie.
Ferdinand.
She used to call me Fernando.
Did she... ever
mention that name?
Yes... l guess there was..
No, that was Kennedy.
And then there were
Joe, Joel, Jacinto...
John, Peter, Joe.
Mai mentioned many, many names.
What a colorful life she had.
But no, sorry.
She never mentioned
any Fernando.
And that was it, really.
We set out like brave
adventurers to find love.
Look at us...
None of us would know love..
If it punched us in the nose.
Pretending like we knew
anything about anything...
in the first place.
Pretending like we
were wiser now.
I wanted to tell Ferdie
that it was okay.
But he wouldn't understand.
I wanted to tell him
that people die..
"But love never does.
As for Don Pedro, his pan in
our lives was only that much.
I guess he must be stroking
his paintbrush somewhere.
Thinking about Rosie with
his strange kind of love.
So yeah, love never dies.
It's always there, somewhere.
And sometimes you
just have to find it.
Even if there's no unsent
letter waiting at your door.
If love doesn't come
knocking, just knock.
Even if there is no door.
Our time is now now now now
Hey you, c'mon you
You sing and I hear
Laughter in your eyes is clearer
I just want you nearer
Whrill me, frill me
Right now and maybe after
King and queen and up high
Dreaming gold life style
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
Hey you, see you
You and your shadow darling
Silver balls are fire
Soothing my desire
Sing me, ring me
Out in the desert calling
Shifting sans deliver
My hold mine's queer
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
O, my Fanny, is so witty.
O, my Fanny, is so sweet.
O, my Fanny, madam
makes me dither.
O, my Fanny, takes my life..
O Fanny.
Shake your booty on the floor..
The parcel of my dreams is lost.
How much did I cry! What
do I tell you Fanny..
Yes, by God.. This
is a din road.
Now you only tell your PIN code.
O, my Fanny is so funky
O, my Fanny, is a
complete drama company
O, my Fanny is a butterfly,
she flies away..
O, I am not able to
catch my Fanny..
Hey“
Shake your booty on the floor
Hey.. Shake your
booty on the floor
O Faniya.. O Faniya..
Shake your booty on the floor
Shut the faniya man!
Just star-t the car
when I tell you.
Savio. - Yes.
Thanks.
For what?
I love her.
I really love her.
Hey, Savio.
The days in which I
had to fall in love.
I spent all those days
writing letters to you.
O Fanny Re...
All the happiness's of my life.
Got killed as I was lost in the
thoughts of Your whereabouts.
O Fanny Re...
O my beloved!
Now what?
Now... now what? We've
run out of petrol.
O Fanny Re...
Our time is now now now now
Hey you, c'mon you
You sing and I hear
Laughter in your eyes is clearer
I just want you nearer
Whrill me, frill me
Right now and maybe after
King and queen and up high
Dreaming gold life style
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
Hey you, see you
You and your shadow darling
Silver balls are fire
Soothing my desire
Sing me, ring me
Out in the desert calling
Shifting sans deliver
My hold mine's queer
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
O, my Fanny, is so witty.
O, my Fanny, is so sweet.
O, my Fanny, madam
makes me dither.
O, my Fanny, takes my life..
O Fanny.
Shake your booty on the floor..
The parcel of my dreams is lost.
How much did I cry! What
do I tell you Fanny..
Yes, by God.. This
is a din road.
Now you only tell your PIN code.
O, my Fanny is so funky
O, my Fanny, is a
complete drama company
O, my Fanny is a butterfly,
she flies away..
O, I am not able to
catch my Fanny..
Hey“
Shake your booty on the floor
Hey.. Shake your
booty on the floor
O Faniya.. O Faniya..
Shake your booty on the floor
Shut the faniya man!
Just star-t the car
when I tell you.
Savio. - Yes.
Thanks.
For what?
I love her.
I really love her.
Hey, Savio.
The days in which I
had to fall in love.
I spent all those days
writing letters to you.
O Fanny Re...
All the happiness's of my life.
Got killed as I was lost in the
thoughts of Your whereabouts.
O Fanny Re...
O my beloved!
Now what?
Now... now what? We've
run out of petrol.
O Fanny Re...
Our time is now now now now
Hey you, c'mon you
You sing and I hear
Laughter in your eyes is clearer
I just want you nearer
Whrill me, frill me
Right now and maybe after
King and queen and up high
Dreaming gold life style
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
Hey you, see you
You and your shadow darling
Silver balls are fire
Soothing my desire
Sing me, ring me
Out in the desert calling
Shifting sans deliver
My hold mine's queer
The sky was high but we believed
We here to stay
We show them how
Our growing light.
Our growing need.
We blazed away
Our time is now now now now now!
O, my Fanny, is so witty.
O, my Fanny, is so sweet.
O, my Fanny, madam
makes me dither.
O, my Fanny, takes my life..
O Fanny.
Shake your booty on the floor..
The parcel of my dreams is lost.
How much did I cry! What
do I tell you Fanny..
Yes, by God.. This
is a din road.
Now you only tell your PIN code.
O, my Fanny is so funky
O, my Fanny, is a
complete drama company
O, my Fanny is a butterfly,
she flies away..
O, I am not able to
catch my Fanny..
Hey
Shake your booty on the floor
Hey.. Shake your
booty on the floor
O Faniya.. O Faniya..
Shake your booty on the floor
Shut the faniya man!
♪ Hope it helped -> bozxphd ♪