'receive General Anaesthesia.'
'Most of them'
'fall asleep peacefully.'
'But a few are not so fortunate.'
'They get trapped in
a frightening phenomenon'
'called Anaesthesia Awareness.'
'These patients remain conscious'
'but are completely paralysed.'
'They can hear sounds, '
'and experience pain'
'but are unable to scream
for help.'
'The cause of this remains a mystery.'
Subtitle by Vishal & Jio
Some wine, ma'am?
- Thank you.
All the business days...
I heard that.
Yeah.
Oh God, I am late.
Just where the hell is
that interpreter?
These two morons are giving me
bloody migraine.
Alright. Thank you.
Thanks.
No!
Alright.
- Maybe we shouldn't.
It might have religious sentiments.
Like I care.
'There were a lot of
beautiful women at the party, '
'but I couldn't take
my eyes off her.'
'She was definitely special.'
'That's probably because she
didn't seem to be from this world.'
'Just like me.'
'And that's why I liked her.'
Greetings, Mrs Singh.
You're Indian, right?
- Yes.
My name is Ria.
I am the guest relations officer
with this hotel,
and a part time interpreter too.
Thank God.
At least someone speaks Hindi here.
Well nowadays, most Indians
prefer to speak English,
but our guests don't.
That's why you were brought in
to help.
- Okay.
Hi, mom.
- Adi.
You should have gotten here
before I did.
You know how important
this deal is for us.
I know.
Hi.
- Hi.
Well, as you know my husband
Vikram Singh started this company,
Vikramaditya Group Of Industries,
15 years ago.
Today, as we go global,
I wish he was alive to see this.
'I wish he was alive to see this.'
Aditya my son here handles the
international business division.
Don't be fooled by his chocolate looks.
There is a sharp business mind with
an international finance degree
behind it that works non-stop.
Arabic!
When did you learn Arabic?
That's all the Arabic I know.
- Hey, Adam!
One second.
Excuse me. I have to go.
Excuse me.
- Please wait.
They do not bother to understand
our people, our language or our country.
The Americans gave us slavery,
we gave them presidents for two terms.
You knew he could speak English!
What's so funny?
You may go now.
'She didn't know what she had done.'
My mom was upset with her.
And she would never be forgiven
for her mistake.
I am sure that we will enjoy
a mutually respectful
and beneficial relationship.
You give us the raw material and
we will give you a honest price.
Together we will explore new markets.
Deal?
- Deal.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen, dinner is served.
After you, ma'am.
Okay. Come.
Well, Mr Ali, I hope you've been
enjoying your stay at the hotel here.
If there is anything you need,
please feel free to call Aditya.
He will always be available.
'Well, as you know my husband
Vikram Singh started this company'
'Vikramaditya Group Of Industries,
15 years ago.'
'Today, as we go global'
'I wish he was alive to see this.'
'I am sorry, dad.'
'Adi!'
- Save him.
'Dad!'
'Adi!'
Sorry, mom.
20 missed calls, Adi.
Where had you been?
It's rude
to leave the guests without
informing anyone.
I got tired, mom,
so I came to my room.
And I dozed off.
And where are you now?
I am in the room.
- Really?
Shit!
'He got there first.'
'Klinsmann challenging him.'
'Putting Klinsmann in the game
on the far side.'
Clause 77 B doesn't seem
right in the contract.
We shouldn't give them
so much advantage.
What do you think, Adi?
'Goes off for the challenge.'
'Argentina down to ten men.
The first man ever'
'to be sent off in a world cup final.'
Your entire generation will go deaf
before they turn 40.
The volume is too high.
I can't even hear myself.
Hello.
My phone is ringing somewhere.
Over there. It's not here.
'I'm a great admirer
of German football.'
'They have played some of the best games
over the last 15 years.'
Hello.
'There's no question, it's a foul.'
I can't hear anything.
Set the TV on mute.
'Not been...'
Sorry. Yes, tell me.
'Hello, Mrs Singh, I am speaking
from the Parulkar Heart Institute.'
'We have found a donor.
Can you come here tomorrow?'
But I am in Dubai and I've a very
important meeting tomorrow morning.
'Ma'am, we have found a donor
with great difficulty.'
'You won't get such
an opportunity again.'
Fine. I will be there. Bye.
Adi, I am going back.
I will take the morning flight.
Oh God, I hate this!
I hate to leave you here.
This isn't the first time.
Adi, you've to sign the deal
on Monday. Don't forget.
I don't know how we will pull this off.
It's a weekend.
Why are you going?
What could be more important for you
than this multi-million dollar contract?
Huh?
You.
But I am here.
Adi, they found a perfect match,
after trying for two years.
That's not the perfect match.
I don't like it.
What are you talking about?
You're going to Mumbai to meet
Trehan, right? - Yes, but...
Stop talking nonsense.
Monday at 11 AM. Don't oversleep.
Adi,
I've worked hard for
the company's success.
Now, this is the next big step.
But first, I want you to be
completely okay.
Yeah.
'I've told you many times that
I don't want a heart transplant.'
'But you've always done'
'what you want.'
Okay?
- Thank you very much.
Thanks.
- Thanks.
I hate to leave you over here.
Don't sleep late in the night,
and don't forget to take your vitamins
after breakfast. Did you hear me?
Yes.
Will you wake up in time for breakfast?
Okay, mom. I will wake up
and take my vitamins as well.
I will take care of everything.
You should get going,
otherwise you'll miss your flight.
You seem to be in hurry
to send me away.
Take care.
- Love you, mom.
See you. Don't roam around much. Okay?
- Okay, mom.
Alright. Bye.
- Bye.
'What do I wish for?'
'What is this feeling?'
'The one I didn't know until yesterday, '
'is with me every moment now.'
'Which colour is this?'
'Whose company is this?'
'What is this rhythm?'
'Whose voice is this?'
'Why do I feel restless?'
'Why does her fragrance
enthral me?'
'I haven't met her yet.'
'Why then'
'is she always around?'
'What do I wish for?'
'What is this feeling?'
♪ O Lord, tell me
what's happening to me. ♪
♪ I have lost my heart
for the first time. ♪
♪ My eyes search for her
everywhere. ♪
♪ I don't know how I lost my heart. ♪
♪ Since I've seen you, all my
desires seem to have awakened. ♪
♪ For once, come to me and
give me your heart, for God's sake. ♪
♪ My darling, I'm crazy about you.
How will I ♪
♪ survive without you? ♪
♪ My darling, I live for you. ♪
♪ O my beloved. ♪
♪ Why does love hurt so much? ♪
♪ I feel restless day and night. ♪
♪ Without You, I don't even
feel like breathing. ♪
♪ You tell me what to do? ♪
♪ Take my joy and give me
all your sorrow. ♪
♪ For I am yours. ♪
♪ I'll forget the world and
lose myself just for you. ♪
♪ My darling, I'm crazy about you.
How will I ♪
♪ survive without you? ♪
♪ My darling, I live for you. ♪
♪ O my beloved. ♪
♪ I believe, I'm alive and I know
that this is love. ♪
♪ Nobody means more to me than you. ♪
♪ I can tell that to the world. ♪
♪ Far away from
the people and this world, ♪
♪ I reside in your heart. ♪
♪ Let me hide in your eyes
and vanish without a trace. ♪
♪ Test me if you wish, but make me yours
so that nothing comes between us. ♪
♪ My darling, I'm crazy about you.
How will I ♪
♪ survive without you? ♪
♪ My darling, I live for you. ♪
♪ O my beloved. ♪
Do you want white powder?
Hey, do you want white powder?
It's good quality. Do you want some?
Dude, want some cocaine?
White powder. It's really fresh stuff.
Everybody buys it from me.
So, you want some?
It's amazing stuff.
- I don't do drugs, man. Seriously.
Okay, listen,
would you like to buy diamonds?
I've got d-class VVS.
It's five carat
at 25 percent jewellery price.
It's amazing Dubai's stuff.
Would you like to buy it?
Tell me if you want to buy.
Want it?
Let's go.
Come on.
You're going to love this, bro.
Good.
- Yes.
Very good.
10,000 dollars.
Ten dollars.
What are you saying, man?
10,000 dollars!
Ten dollars.
- What?
Check this out, bro.
I know the class, cut, caratage
and clarity of this diamond.
It's all good.
I do diamonds, you see.
You were going to give
this to me, weren't you?
As far as I know, it's a fake.
But anyway, you know what?
I like your style.
I will take it.
Ten dollars.
Damn! You short played me, man!
By the way,
if you deal in real diamonds,
what will you do with a fake?
It may be a fake for you,
but for me, it's real.
It's the first independent deal
of my life.
It's party time.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
- One espresso please.
Sure.
Hey.
Keep the change.
- Thank you, sir.
Screwed, man.
I don't know how to thank you, Trehan.
Sanjeev.
Gayatri,
don't raise your hopes too much.
I've already told you that a transplant
doesn't guarantee anything.
This surgery has
a minimal success rate.
The body could reject the heart
even after a transplant.
And if Adi doesn't want
to undergo surgery,
his attitude will further reduce
his chances.
Let me deal with his attitude.
I will convince him.
Now that we have found a donor,
it will be easy to convince him.
I have a request, Sanjeev.
You must perform the surgery.
I can't trust anyone else.
You know what Adi means to me.
Of course, Gayatri.
I will explain the entire procedure
to you tomorrow.
I have the tapes of some surgeries that
I had performed.
You can see them.
- Okay.
You'll get an idea.
Oh! It's 1:30.
Lunch?
I am really tired. I'm came here
directly from the airport.
Rain check?
But you will eat, won't you?
I don't want to go out.
Besides,
I've to talk to Adi.
I'll just take two minutes.
Pass.
Here.
Man!
Come back here.
'No, Adi, you can't play football.'
Give the ball. Pass the ball.
Please, give the ball.
Come on, man.
- Sorry.
I am coming there.
Okay.
- Pass the ball.
That's our ball.
- Chill, guys.
Yes!
Hey, mom.
Hi, Adi.
- Did you reach safely?
How's the temperature?
- The temperature!
It's Mumbai. Always the same.
Not Mumbai. I am talking about
Trehan's temperature.
Oh! Shut up.
Where are you?
- Mom, I am just chilling.
Hanging out, you know.
No late nights, okay? Please.
You too, mom. Please!
Okay.
Mom, I got to go. Okay?
Love you, mom. Bye.
- Bye.
Make it.
Naughty fellow.
Come.
- Thanks.
Children grow up, Gayatri.
A single woman like you
should think about her life.
Adi is my life.
By the way, Sanjeev, how is Ila?
She is good, I guess.
She is on
her third vacation trip this year.
Malay forests.
Gayatri, you know that
we were together just for the children.
And now, the children have
all grown up.
I take your leave.
And thanks once again.
Okay.
Don't touch me!
'Hey, how are you, baby?'
Dare touch me!
- The camera...
Baby!
- Leave me alone.
What's your price, baby?
- Come with us.
Wow! You're looking so hot.
Hey!
What's your rate, baby?
- Look at her. Yeah!
Hey!
Who are you waving at?
Hey.
- We are here. Who are you waving at?
Stop it!
Oh, wow! Look at her.
Hey, guys!
Yes. Who is he?
- Who are you?
Are you guys tourists?
Hey, dude, buzz off.
Yeah, right.
Hi.
Hey, who are you? Back off.
Alright...
Sure. She needs to go too.
Come on.
- Hey, wait.
Back off, wise guy!
- Get going, dude.
Do you know her?
Yes.
- No.
What an idiot!
Run!
- Catch them!
What was that?
- Pepper spray.
What?
Do you always carry it?
- Yes.
So that I can save people like you.
What? Run.
Run.
Stop running!
Okay, Lara Croft,
we are safe now.
I am Ria.
- Okay.
Ria.
Do you remember the way to hotel?
May be.
You shouldn't roam around alone.
It's dangerous.
Can I drop you to the hotel?
Yeah, sure.
But where is the car?
I don't have a car.
No car. How do we get there?
Okay, let's walk.
- Let's go.
You're on a business trip, right?
- Yeah.
But your mom went back.
Are you on a holiday?
- No.
It was the weekend,
so I stayed back.
Are you a local?
No. I am from Afghanistan.
- Oh!
I lost my parents in a car bombing.
I was the only survivor.
I am sorry.
I couldn't forgive myself
for a long time
for having survived.
But then I thought I should live
their share of life as well.
Perhaps, I will find peace.
Since then life's been good.
It's just been a month
since I came here.
Earlier I was at the Cairo branch
of the same hotel.
Oh!
That's why you speak Arabic!
Yes, you're right.
- Okay.
Here we are.
Well, thank you
for saving me from the goons
and bringing me here safe and sound.
Would you like to have coffee?
Hotel staff
can't socialise with
the guests at the hotel.
There are rules. Sorry.
Bye.
Congrats, Mr Singh.
- Here we go.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Cheers to our alliance, Mr Ali.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Together we will conquer new horizons.
And Adi,
well done. I am proud of you.
Now, come home soon.
Miss you.
- I miss you too.
Just signing the deal isn't enough.
The manufacturing and delivery
should be exactly as per schedule.
Make new schedules. I want to see them.
But there's place in our schedule
for this new order.
Then make the schedule accordingly.
- But ma'am...
Our workers are already
working two shifts.
We can't push them.
There can be a third shift.
I don't want excuses.
What if the workers refuse?
Then replace them.
Okay.
Mr Mahajan,
I pay you to find the answers,
not to ask questions.
Just do it.
- Okay.
Radhika, come with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Adi's ticket is confirmed.
Don't forget to send a car for him.
Ma'am, Mr Singh has extended his trip.
He isn't arriving tomorrow.
- What?
Why didn't you tell me?
How can he change the ticket
without asking me?
Call him.
- Okay.
'The number you're trying to reach
is currently not reachable.'
Switched off.
Hi!
Let's go out for a stroll.
Sorry, I am on duty.
Your Mr Adam Kowalski has booked me
for interpretation.
- Oh!
I asked him to do that.
What?
- Yes.
Let's go. Come on.
Why do you need an interpreter?
- I don't.
Come on. Let's go. I want you
to show me Dubai today.
Come on. Sit.
♪ Whenever I see you, you seem divine. ♪
♪ I wonder what's the connection
between us. ♪
♪ Whenever I see you, you seem divine. ♪
♪ I wonder what's the connection
between us. ♪
♪ I wonder why I look for ways
to get close to you. ♪
♪ By God, I will leave this world
if you say so. ♪
♪ It's mesmerising, your smile. ♪
♪ It's enchanting, when you blush. ♪
♪ You affect me.
I want to make you mine. ♪
♪ It's mesmerising, your smile. ♪
♪ It's enchanting, when you blush. ♪
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
♪ Your eyes speak a million words. ♪
♪ My heart skips a beat
at a mere glimpse of you. ♪
♪ I was so lonely before I met you. ♪
♪ It seems I was waiting for you. ♪
♪ Let me stare at you for a while,
if you don't mind. ♪
♪ It's mesmerising, your smile. ♪
♪ It's enchanting, when you blush. ♪
♪ I'm in love. ♪
♪ I miss you day and night. ♪
♪ You mean more to me than life. ♪
♪ Take me in your arms
and hold me tight. ♪
♪ I want to be with you all my life. ♪
♪ Let's get closer and make sure
nothing ever gets between us. ♪
♪ It's mesmerising, your smile. ♪
♪ It's enchanting, when you blush. ♪
♪ Whenever I see you, you seem divine. ♪
♪ I wonder what's the connection
between us. ♪
♪ I wonder why I look for ways
to get close to you. ♪
♪ By God, I will leave this world
if you say so. ♪
♪ It's mesmerising, your smile. ♪
♪ It's enchanting, when you blush. ♪
♪ My darling... ♪
♪ Come closer. ♪
Okay. Good night.
Hold on, Ria.
Just a moment.
This is for you.
Do you like it?
Why are you giving this to me?
No particular reason.
Without rhyme or reason?
- Yes.
We spend a lovely time together,
so I thought I should give you a gift.
So that we can have
a lot more fun next time.
Fun?
- Yes.
Next time?
I thought you're different from others,
but you're worse than them.
- What?
They are what they seem to be.
Who do you think you are?
Did you think
a diamond ring will make me
jump into your arms?
You think you can buy me!
Do you think I am for sale? Here.
Wait. No, Ria...
Ria, listen to me.
Just leave me alone. Go away.
- Let me explain.
I was just kidding.
You are getting it wrong. It's just...
It's just a ring. Come on.
Come on, man. Give me a break.
Ria, that guy has been staring
at you for a very long time.
What's his problem?
Cheers!
What the hell is going on?
Stop it.
Just stop it!
I have just begun.
What do you want?
I want you to listen to me carefully.
And then do whatever you want.
Go ahead.
Come with me.
- Look, it's the same girl.
Yes, pal.
- So, what's her price?
Ten dollars.
And she thought it was extravagant.
Do you get it now?
I bought the diamond ring
for just ten dollars.
Why didn't you tell me?
Excuse me.
Did you give me a chance?
Before you gave it to me, you idiot!
I don't like trophy boyfriends.
Trophy boyfriends?
- Yes.
They have credit cards, but no hearts.
For them,
money speaks louder than words.
I avoid such people.
I am looking for someone
who is simple
and kind hearted.
I am not good at heart, Ria.
'Perhaps, I was at a point in my life'
'from where I couldn't go back'
'or move forward.'
'It was as simple as that'
'and as complicated.'
Adi!
Adi.
Oh my God!
What's wrong?
Open your mouth. Quickly.
Somebody help!
Adi, what happened to you?
Adi.
I told you
I am not good at heart.
Adi!
Good morning.
Nothing to worry.
All your reports are normal.
You scared me.
You gave me a new life.
You've also changed my life.
We are quits.
I can't do this.
You shouldn't be here. You have to go.
When I am not worried about the future,
why are you afraid?
♪ Love is the Lord's blessing.
Love is everyoneâ s wish. ♪
♪ Love is a prayer, my beloved. ♪
♪ Everybody has written about love.
Everybody has studied love. ♪
♪ Everybody falls in love, my beloved. ♪
♪ Yet nobody knows what love means. ♪
♪ Why shouldnâ t I worship you? ♪
♪ My beloved! ♪
♪ I know now that love is divine. ♪
♪ Yet nobody knows what love means. ♪
♪ How do I tell you what happened to me? ♪
♪ Wherever I see, I find you. ♪
♪ I am not at peace without you. ♪
♪ I dream about you every moment. ♪
♪ I know you inside out. ♪
♪ I am so smitten by you. ♪
♪ My heart asks with every beat ♪
♪ why shouldn't I worship you. ♪
♪ My beloved! ♪
♪ I know now that love is divine. ♪
♪ Yet nobody knows what love means. ♪
♪ Love is the Lord's blessing.
Love is everyoneâ s wish. ♪
♪ Everybody has written about love.
Everybody has studied love. ♪
♪ Everybody falls in love, my beloved. ♪
Good morning.
I will just get ready. Okay?
Adi.
Ria.
- What?
I can't do this.
Of course, you can.
Now we are together.
We will do it.
Ria,
we can't let our emotions
get the better of us.
Our emotions are overwhelming, Adi.
Are you having second thoughts about me?
What happened to you
all of a sudden, Aditya?
Listen to me, Adi.
I know you're scared.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Let's just live the moment.
Let's not worry about the future.
That's the problem, Ria.
This relationship is like my life.
It has no future.
Please end this relationship.
You deserve better.
You're right.
You don't have a future.
But I do.
Do you know why?
Because you measure life
by the years you live.
Whereas I live in the moment.
I await a better life,
whereas you await death.
Hence, don't even think that you
are doing me a favour by
ending this relationship.
You don't have the courage
to live, Aditya.
You're a coward.
Have a safe tour back to India,
Mr Singh.
Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Hey, bro!
Hey, Adi.
- What's up?
So nice to see you.
I missed you, Sam.
- Missed you too.
How are you?
- I'm fine. Thank you. What about you?
Fantastic.
- What a pleasant surprise!
When did you return from Dubai?
- This morning.
What did you bring for me?
Sorry, no gifts.
No. That's okay.
Rich people usually give gifts
to those who don't need them.
Stop it, Sam.
Sam, I want to get the transplant done.
I'm ready for it.
- I knew it.
I knew it.
You haven't returned empty-handed.
You have an interesting story
to tell me.
Tell me, hurry up.
- Patience. By the way,
new car, right? I love it.
Enjoying the false pride.
I'm getting late for the clinic.
Come, let's talk on the way.
- Okay. Let's go.
Her name is Ria.
Ria?
- Yeah.
Oh! She's the magician
who made you change your decision.
You kept refusing for so long
and now all of a sudden you're
ready for the operation!
Ria seems to be an amazing girl.
How did she manage to convince you?
She must've done it affectionately.
'You don't have the courage
to live, Aditya.'
'You're a coward.'
Does your mom know?
'No escape.
- No way, mom.'
'I'm so happy, Adi.'
'I wanted to talk to you about
the transplant.'
She must be very excited to know
that you are ready for the transplant.
She must have spoken to
the Dr Trehan by now.
You will perform the surgery, Sam.
Think about the risk, Adi.
More often than not
such complicated cases end in failure.
When you have someone like Dr Trehan
and his team, why do you want me?
I don't like Trehan.
Come on, Adi.
He's a reputed heart surgeon.
He's perfect for the surgery.
His only drawback is that
he is crazy about your mom.
So what's wrong with that?
- Yeah.
After all, you are crazy about
someone too.
Whatever.
Let's see.
Hello.
- Hey, mom.
Hi.
- Hi, Adi.
Dr Trehan and I wanted to see
what's special about this hospital
that you insist on
undergoing surgery over here.
How can you pass judgement
even before getting inside?
Come on, Adi. I am sensible enough
to understand.
Relax, Gayatri.
The success of an operation
doesn't merely depend on the hospital.
It also requires competent hands
and experience.
Let me deal with this.
I want to carry out some tests.
Okay.
- I want to do some fresh tests on Adi.
If you're talking about me,
talk to me.
Listen, son...
- I'm not your son.
Adi!
Please, don't try to be my dad.
Let me tell you this, mom.
Dr Trehan doesn't need to do all this.
Sam will operate on me.
Are you crazy?
How can he perform such a big surgery?
Although we have Dr Trehan with us!
Sam is my friend, mom.
No doctor would care more
for my life than him.
He saved my life once
and you know that, right?
What made you think
that I will allow it?
Mom, you didn't hear me.
I'm not asking you.
I'm just informing you.
This is ridiculous.
I won't allow some run-off-the-mill
doctor to operate on my son.
Adi.
I'll be in my office. Call me later.
Bye, Mrs Singh.
Bye, Dr Trehan.
- Sam...
Adi, we need to talk about this, okay?
Call me.
'I have complete faith in Sam.'
'He's my friend, '
'father and brother.'
'Everything.'
'Now, '
'he's going to give me
a new lease of life.'
♪ It's no longer a rugged
road when you're around. ♪
♪ Every journey becomes fun
when you're with me. ♪
♪ You're a shade in the sunshine. ♪
♪ You're the guiding
force in my life. ♪
♪ I share a lot of good
memories with you. ♪
♪ I want to say this
to you every moment. ♪
♪ Thanks brother, for being there. ♪
Sam,
we have been trying to find
Ria for the last two months.
But we haven't got any information
about her yet.
I don't know what to do.
I cannot live without her.
On an aircraft, we're told
to wear the oxygen
masks ourselves first
before helping others.
Likewise, you need to get well first.
Then we'll find Ria.
Have patience.
We're already late.
On top of that, it has started raining.
The governor had to throw a party today.
Who's she?
Mom, she's Ria.
She's my friend Harshad's sister.
Something seems to be wrong.
You carry on. I'll be with you shortly.
Come soon, I'll send
the car back for you.
Let me take you to the car.
Bye.
Ria, I'm so happy to see you.
I thought we would never meet again.
I don't believe this.
When did you come here?
And how?
I tried a lot to forget you,
but couldn't.
That's why, I'm here. But you...
You didn't even acknowledge
me in front of your mom.
I'm such an idiot
to have come all the way here for you.
Ria, listen to me.
I love you.
Come inside.
Please.
What about your mom?
Mom, she's Ria.
- I know.
I remember her now.
Is she not the girl who
was an interpreter in Dubai?
You lied to me that she
was your friend's sister.
This is unfair.
You know this is a diplomatic function.
You cannot bring any
random person here.
Let's go home.
Tell her to arrange for her
stay somewhere else.
Mom...
You are not the only person
she knows here.
Mom, stop it.
She doesn't know anyone here.
How can I leave her alone?
Besides, it's quite late.
She should have thought about
it before coming here.
She loves me, mom.
That's why she didn't
bother about anything.
But you won't understand.
Because...
She cannot come inside.
Are you coming inside?
You have decided already.
As usual.
Hey, Sam.
- Hi, Adi.
It's quite late. Is everything okay?
Come on in.
Just a second, Sam.
I have someone with me.
Come.
Ria.
- Ria!
Are you kidding me?
Hi, Ria.
- Hello.
Sorry, I cannot take her anywhere else,
so I brought her here.
- Get inside, first. Come on.
Come on.
'The number you've dialled is
currently unavailable.'
'Please try again later.'
'The number you've...'
Okay.
Adi, speak to your mom once.
She must have calmed down by now.
I can imagine her shock
when she saw Ria.
You should have told her before.
Anyway, not too late even now.
Trust me, everything will be fine.
You're right, Sam.
I should go home.
- Wait a second, Adi.
My entire team is coming to
my house tomorrow morning.
If they see Ria here...
I mean, I'm unmarried...
They might misconstrue...
I don't care.
But Ria...
♪ Let my eyes close slowly. ♪
♪ Let me fall asleep. ♪
♪ Let sleep sweep me away
into a beautiful dream. ♪
Ria.
- Yes?
Marry me.
What!
Right now.
Marry me.
It's five o' clock in the morning.
'The number you have
dialled is busy.'
Gayatri, I have already told you.
When children grow up,
you have to let go.
He's not like others, he needs me.
He should accept this.
But he's not thinking straight.
He's taken a wrong decision.
Forget about it.
If he has already decided,
you cannot impose your decision on him.
You need to be positive.
When a drop of water
swells a bit,
it speaks as if the ocean.
Lamps would have been blown out by now,
but there's someone
who prevents the wind.
No one can defy the verdict
passed by the supreme authority.
Mr Singh, please sign here.
Take this.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hear! Hear!
Congratulations! From now on you
are husband and wife. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Congrats!
Love you, Sam.
- Love you too, Adi.
♪ I have found a place in your heart. ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
♪ Your heartbeats brought me all the way
to your heart. ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
♪ You and me, gradually, nervously,
fell in love. ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
♪ At times, somewhere or the other,
when you are nearby... ♪
when you are nearby, ♪
♪ I am somehow convinced. ♪
♪ that you are meant to be with me
forever and ever. ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
♪ I have found a place in your heart. ♪
♪ Your heartbeats brought me all the way
to your heart. ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
♪ You and me, gradually, nervously,
fell in love. ♪
♪ Are you feeling what I'm feeling? ♪
♪ What a feeling! ♪
What happened, Aditya?
I got a call from Sam.
I'm sorry, Aditya.
I had to call you all
of a sudden because
we found donor all of a sudden.
I hope you're completely
prepared for the operation.
I guess.
Hi! Are you Mr Aditya Singh?
- Yes.
Your mom is waiting for you
at the reception area
along with Dr Trehan.
Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
How did you come to know that
I was getting operated today?
I'm your mom.
Just a second.
Adi.
I'm very happy
that you have agreed to undergo surgery.
But...
I still believe that
Sam is not the...
Adi, listen.
There's still time. Think about it.
Sam is not the right man
to conduct the surgery.
Dr Trehan should be doing it.
He's the best.
Okay?
God bless you.
I have decided already, mom.
Okay?
I'll see you soon. Okay.
I love you, mom.
- I love you too.
Bye.
Okay.
It's time to say good
bye to each other.
Only two minutes.
Thank you, Sam.
- Anytime.
You know what?
We'll start afresh
once you are out of the hospital.
Ria.
- Yes?
Will my new heart love you as much as
this one does?
Yes.
- I love you.
I love you too.
Okay, love birds, time up.
Can we get some more time?
- No.
Love you.
See you soon, my dear wife.
Say that again.
I think you should leave.
There is nothing you can really do.
Sure?
- Yes.
Call me if you need anything.
- Okay.
Take care.
You?
- I am Mrs Ria Aditya Singh.
When?
What?
When did my son get married?
When?
A few days ago.
Hi, guys.
I am Dr Gupta.
You can call me Gups.
Pleasure meeting you all.
Hello. Oh!
I would have shook your hand,
but you know...
Well, all set?
What's going on, Prakash?
Who is he?
I don't know. Your friend Patkar
is down with laryngitis.
That why he is here.
But I need Patkar.
- Even I want him,
but Gupta replaced him.
Well, no problem.
The anaesthetist may have changed,
but the operation is the same.
- Yes.
Come.
Hi, Dr Gupta. Let me introduce myself.
I am Dr Sameer Saxena.
You can call me Sam. - Hello.
This is Dr Prakash Solanki.
He is Dr Ajit Rathore. - Hello.
And this is my theatre assistant,
Jenny D'souza.
Hi, Jenny.
So, how's the patient feeling?
I am fine.
Is everything alright, Sam?
Just fine, Adi.
Hey, Jenny.
I will see you after the break.
Okay.
So Adi, this is it.
Yeah.
When you regain consciousness,
we will be done with all this.
I hope so.
See you soon.
See you soon, Sam.
Dr Gupta.
- Yes?
He is my friend. Be careful. Okay?
Okay.
Increase the supply of oxygen.
- Yes, doctor.
Well.
They must have asked you what you
have eaten in the past four hours.
Yes.
You must have received
general anaesthesia previously.
Am I right?
- Yes.
I read your pre-operative assessment
and have made a special recipe for you.
It's a cocktail.
I am sure,
you are going to like it.
Here we go.
Start counting backwards from ten.
I can't.
- What?
At school I learned to count straight.
I am just kidding. I am so scared.
Okay, relax. You will be fine.
Here we go.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Happy journey, my friend.
Let yourself go.
Okay. Let's get going.
Hey, Gups, what did you give him?
Midazolam, fentanyl,
and a bit of vecuronium chaser.
'God!'
'Will the surgery leave a scar?'
'Use some shaving cream, at least.'
'Ew! What is that smell?'
'But how do I know all this?'
'I should be unconscious, right?'
'I don't know how much time it takes
for an anaesthetic to take effect.'
All okay, Gupta?
He is sleeping like a log.
- 'Yeah, right!'
Shall we begin?
- 'Wait a minute.'
'Are you starting the operation?'
'I should be unconscious, right?'
'Why do I hear everyone's voices?'
Ready, guys?
- 'How am I feeling all this?'
'Sam, something is wrong!'
'I think the anaesthesia
didn't work on me!'
Alright, get the drips on.
- 'Guys!'
'Hello! Something is not right!'
'No, Sam!'
Check on that monitor.
- 'I can hear everything.'
'I am not unconscious, Sam!'
'I am in my senses!'
Okay, Gupta.
- 'Stop this!'
'Someone please take a look!'
'Take a look at the machines!'
'Look at the bloody monitor, Sam!'
Scalpel.
- 'Stop, Sam!'
'Oh God! No!'
'Please, stop it!'
Do we have blood?
- 'Open your eyes, Adi!'
'No, Sam!'
'I'm in a lot of pain!'
'Stop it, Sam!'
'The pain is unbearable! Sam, please!'
Make sure the scalpel is
sharper next time. - 'Sam!'
'Please.'
Saw.
- 'Please, Sam!'
'Don't do this!'
- Okay.
'Sam!'
'No, Sam!'
'Sam, please stop it!'
'I can't bear this anymore!'
'Sam!'
'Think of something else
to forget the pain, Adi!'
Drips go uniform there.
- 'Think about something else!'
Prakash get ready to clamp.
- 'Distract yourself!'
'Think about Ria!'
'Ria!'
'Help me!'
'Ria, please save me!'
'Ria! That's it!'
'Ria!'
'Focus on Ria, Adi.'
'The memories of Ria!'
'Think about Ria!'
'Ria!'
'Focus.'
'No! Not this!'
'Shit! What? No!'
'No! Not this, Adi!'
'Think about something else.
- I've a lot to do at the office.'
'And if I don't work, your dad's dream
won't be fulfilled'
'and this business
will be shut down.'
'No, Adi, you can't play football.'
'Stop it.'
'You snatch everything.
You take away all the things I like.'
'I hate you!'
'At least agree to go for
a heart transplant.'
'No.
- You owe it to yourself.'
'No. I told you once.'
'That's it.
- Help me!'
'Sam!'
'What's the patient's name?
- Aditya Singh.'
'He is experiencing
severe chest pain and heaviness.'
'And he is hemodynamically unstable.'
'A possible myocardial infarction.'
'Sam, you saved me
the first time I had an attack.'
'Sam, please do something.'
'Don't worry, Aditya,
everything will be alright.'
'Stay with me, pal.'
'Stay with me.'
- Wait.
Open it nice and well.
'What the hell! The same pain again.'
'Don't worry, Adi. You will be fine.'
- That's it.
'You can control it
like you did earlier.'
'You can do it!'
Another bone broke.
- He'll be in a lot of pain tomorrow.
Sorry, Adi.
'Yes, you better be sorry, Sam!'
'The pain won't last long, Adi.'
'We are nearly through.'
'Sam will fix all this'
'like he did in the past.'
'Stay with me, pal.
Everything is going to be okay.'
'I always follow up on my patients.'
'Especially when I've saved
someone's life. Have a seat.'
'You can thank me.'
'This is the right time.'
'How do I thank you?'
'Well, I prefer cash.'
'Sam, take me to Ria.'
'Adi, you've a rare heart disease
called EMF.'
'You need a heart transplant.'
'Which is fibrosis of heart...
- What are you thinking?'
'Unfortunately, there's no cure'
'except a heart transplant.'
'I love going for the big catch.'
'Do you go fishing? That means you
only like being a millionaire.'
'You like to eat the fish others
work hard to catch.'
'Am I right? He is my dad.'
'She is my mom. Isn't it weird'
'that a person's entire life'
'can be summed up on
a small part of a wall?'
'I hope my life'
'fills the entire wall, at least.'
'Oh God!'
'I miss you, Ria.
- Is this okay?'
'I love you so much.'
'I love you and I miss you.'
'Ria, help me get rid of this pain.'
'Miss you.'
'Look at me, Ria. Just look at me.'
'This operation will over soon, Ria.'
'Very soon, I will be with you.'
'Just pray for me.'
'Ria's memories'
'from the beginning.
- You're rich, handsome, '
'and honest.'
'Wow!'
'How is it your fault'
'that you were born in a rich family?'
'Now it's your turn.'
'Stay with me. Just stay with me'
'We are almost there, Ria.'
'Almost there.'
- The new heart is here, doctor.
It's a beautiful heart.
You're very fortunate.
By the way, I have two tickets
of the IPL game.
Jenny, care to join me?
No, thanks.
I don't like cricket.
- What!
Why?
Hey, Sam.
Will you come with me?
I hate cricket.
What's your problem?
Oh God! Adi's medicines.
I carry them with me.
Otherwise, he takes them every
half hour like chocolates.
He could overdose, you know.
Thank God! He won't need them anymore.
You care a lot about him, don't you?
Nice.
I tried to find reasons
to not like him,
to go far away from him.
Honestly,
I know how important he is to you.
What do you want, Ria?
I just want him to be happy.
And it's linked to your happiness.
He has already lost his dad.
I don't want him to lose you too.
It's not wrong to love someone,
Mrs Singh.
And I am not bad.
Please.
There are some more pills besides these.
- What?
He has some allergies,
especially during summer.
It's okay.
Alright.
Aditya Singh's family?
- Yes.
Ma'am, his operation has started.
The two of you should go to
the waiting room on the second floor.
Okay.
He is sleeping comfortably.
Dr Gupta, you've been working
for a long time.
Why don't you take a break?
Go and have a cup of coffee.
- Oh! That's a good idea.
I need to make a call.
- No problem.
We won't need you for half an hour.
Thanks.
I will join you soon.
Sam, what happened? Are you alright?
I can't do it.
But what's the problem?
Patkar.
- Okay.
He messed it up.
And this new guy, Gupta,
he is keeping an eye on us.
Oh, come on, Sam. Gupta is an idiot.
He doesn't know what's happening here.
No.
I think he is spying on us.
I think he knows everything.
We kept lowering Adi's position on
the list. - 'What!'
Have you ever stood near Gupta?
He's not a spy. He's an alcoholic.
He has a bad hangover.
Hey! Lower your voice.
He will be here soon.
Jenny, go and stand guard outside.
And try to find out what
happened to Patkar.
Sam, you're just getting paranoid.
Nobody will come to know anything.
I have planned all this.
And my instructions will be
followed to the letter.
I don't want to go to jail.
'Jail! What are you
talking about, Sam?'
Nobody is going to jail. Inject
the new heart and put it back inside.
That's all.
- 'What the hell is going on?'
Calm down, Sam. Nobody will have a clue.
Let's finish all this in an hour
and then have a few drinks.
He will be dead by the time
Gupta returns.
'I'll be dead!'
'Oh my God, Adi!'
I don't know why I get a feeling
that Gupta is watching us.
Come on, Sam.
- Come on, Sam.
'Mom! Ria! Save me!'
I am very tense.
Why are they taking so much time?
I'll go and check.
- I'll come with you.
No, you stay here.
Okay, darling, love you.
Hey!
Sam!
Sam, why do you want to kill me?
Why?
I am warning you, guys.
If he gets suspicious,
I'll cancel the plan immediately.
I swear, I am not kidding.
Come off it, Sam.
Excuse me.
- Yes?
Do you know what's the status
of the operation?
The heart transplant.
Aditya Singh?
- Yes.
Oh, he is doing fine.
Everything is going as planned.
Is it?
Yes, I am coming from there.
Any problem?
But you don't seem to be a doctor here.
I mean you don't work at this hospital.
Oh! I am Dr Shashank Gupta.
I am Aditya's anaesthetist.
Pleasure meeting you.
Just excuse me.
Patkar is down with laryngitis
that's why I replaced him.
I'm from St Mary's hospital. - Oh!
Ria.
Ria!
Ria, save me please. Listen to me.
They want to kill me.
Sam is not my friend. Ria, listen to me.
Oh! No, everything is fine.
Give her a kiss from my side.
And tell him I will be home soon.
Ria, ask them.
- What's going on here?
Why is it taking so much time?
What did I do?
What harm had Ria caused you?
Why are you doing this?
Ria, what are you doing here? You
shouldn't be in the operation theatre.
I just came here to see
what's happening.
I was getting worried.
Is everything okay?
- Yes. Everything is fine.
Ria, he is lying.
Really? I spoke to some guy named Gupta.
Our regular anaesthetist Patkar
couldn't make it,
Gupta is his replacement
from St Mary's hospital.
But you don't have to worry.
Everything is alright.
Don't trust him.
He is lying. He is trying to kill me.
Are you sure everything is alright?
But, of course.
Everything is under control.
Bullshit!
- That's it. Come on, baby. Yes!
What's going on here?
Why isn't Patkar here?
I spoke to him. He is at home.
He is at home?
- Yes.
He backed down.
- Backed down!
What do you mean he backed down?
Yes, ask him.
Anyway, I hope Gupta
doesn't suspect anything.
No. Not at all.
What about Adi's mom?
Are you mad? A few minutes ago,
she was in tears and hugging me.
She is under control.
Please get her a gown quickly.
But what about Gupta?
- Don't worry about him.
He is a drunkard. He won't be here
for another half an hour.
Sam, we need to put him
on bypass quickly.
Ria, it was my plan.
I can back out whenever I want.
Sam, you can't back out.
We have worked on this for a year.
I changed my name and my life.
It's all clear.
Nothing will happen to us.
And the toughest part has
already been done.
He married me.
'He is Prakash, the second witness.
- Hi.'
'Are you a doctor too?
- Yes.'
'Sorry, I am late.'
'I was buying a wedding gift for you.'
'I am Jenny.
- Nice to meet you.'
'They knew each other.
- Nice to meet you too. Congrats.'
'Jenny.
- Thank you very much.'
'They were in cahoots
with each other.'
'What are you thinking?'
'I don't believe this.'
Sam, why did you make this plan?
You're in debt.
This is the only way
to pay off your debt.
'Sam is my friend, mom.'
'No doctor would care more
for my life than him.'
Ria, I can't kill him.
Then get ready to die.
Your creditors are not
as amicable as you.
They won't hesitate to kill you.
You have no option, Sam.
Just face it.
Ria, it's just money.
He is my friend.
If I ask him, he will give me the money.
Sam, don't talk nonsense!
- Hey, listen to me.
It was my idea.
He came to me first.
I got all of you involved.
I sent you to Dubai.
I called her mom here
so that you can entrap him.
'Yes, tell me. - Hello, Mrs Singh. I am
calling from Parulkar Heart Institute.'
'We have found a donor.
Can you come here tomorrow?'
'But I am in Dubai and I've a very
important meeting tomorrow morning.'
'Ma'am, we have found a donor
with great difficulty.'
'You won't get such
an opportunity again.'
Had he died before you get married,
my plan would have failed.
Absolutely.
Had I been in your place,
I would have married him
before leaving Dubai.
Really?
But it would have happened
only if you hadn't got pregnant
with your boyfriend's child, Jenny.
So just get lost.
Sam, you're getting emotional now.
But you'll need money in a few days.
And you're going to regret this.
You won't earn such a lot even
if you conduct surgeries all your life.
We stand to get millions.
Even after distributing the
amount equally between
the five of us, you will
have more than enough.
Besides, it's a case of transplant.
Such patients die within a few years.
You're right.
No!
Come on, Sam. Let's move.
Pass the new heart.
But I haven't injected it.
Then do it, Sam.
We don't have time. Damn it!
Where is the syringe?
- Over there.
Give it to me.
- Ria, what are you doing?
Come on move your bloody hand.
Sam, take the syringe, inject it,
and put it back in.
Sam, it was your idea.
So finish it what you began.
Just do it, Sam.
He loves you a lot.
Love!
He doesn't even know me.
We have never met.
Wait. Hold on.
Ria, don't.
Now, put it in.
Sorry, baby.
Mrs Singh.
Is Adi alright?
They didn't tell me anything.
- But you were in there for a long time.
Ria,
I am very scared.
Well, guys, how's everything?
Everything is fine. Forceps.
Hey, you guys seem to be in hurry.
- Dr Gupta,
look what's happening with me.
Dr Gupta, look at me.
There is something wrong with me!
Look at my eyes!
Please look at my eyes! I am crying!
Dr Gupta, look at me!
Just a minute. Stop.
- Yes, Dr Gupta.
I can't go to the IPL game tomorrow.
I forgot that I've to take
my wife to dinner tomorrow.
Dr Rathore,
I'll give you both the tickets.
Take your girlfriend to the game.
She will be very happy.
Something is wrong.
I can feel it.
I can't just sit here doing nothing.
Calm down. Don't worry.
Everything is going to be fine.
I can't live without him.
Pressure down.
'She knew where I kept my pills.'
'Do you think I am for sale? Here.'
'She threw away a ring worth 10 dollars
and became a billionaire.'
'Adi, you're such a fool.'
Ria, I hope you're happy.
There is something wrong.
He is fibbing.
He is fibbing!
Wait a minute. What do we do, Sam?
Start de-fibrillation.
Make it 60 joules.
- Paddle to 60 joules.
'I can't trust a run-of-the-mill
doctor with your life.'
'He is my friend, mom.
I trust him implicitly.'
'The problem is that
you don't trust me.'
'I am so sorry, mom.'
'The number you're calling...'
'Everything was happening
right in front of me, '
'but I had no clue.'
'How could I have known?'
'I was busy looking at you.'
Charge once again.
Paddle charge. Charge released.
- Clear.
Charge.
Clear.
- Give it to me. Let me charge it.
Come on, Adi!
We are losing him.
No, let me give it another try, please.
It's over, Sam.
We need to put him on bypass.
What about adrenaline?
It's pointless.
Let me try one shot of it. Please.
Come on, Adi!
Come on!
- It won't work. It's over.
Are you sure, Dr Gupta, there is no air?
Yes, there is no air.
I can see it.
- Oh, come on, Adi!
Adi!
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all my fault.
No, Sam, it's not your fault.
Oh, come on.
I should have done something.
Sam, you did whatever you could.
Oh, really?
- Yes, Sam.
It wasn't the right heart.
We need to inform his family.
Who will tell them?
I will tell them.
I should do this.
I will come with you.
Sorry, Gayatri.
His body rejected the heart.
We tried a lot,
but the organ failed.
I am so sorry.
The organ failed!
More often than not, in such cases...
- You...
You have failed.
No. We tried our best,
but the procedure...
- Say it.
What?
- Tell me.
I want to hear you say that you failed.
You couldn't save my son.
I knew you shouldn't have
performed the surgery.
You shouldn't have been here.
Sorry, Mrs Singh.
I knew it.
- Mrs Singh.
So sorry.
Adi, I am so sorry.
I am so sorry.
Adi, sorry.
- I am sorry, ma'am,
but we need your permission,
to remove Aditya from the bypass.
My permission?
- Yes.
We need your signature to
take Aditya off the bypass.
I don't get it.
Is he alive?
Yes, technically.
But a machine is pumping the blood.
He doesn't have a heart.
Then, get another heart.
You don't understand.
His blood group is rare.
It's very difficult to get
another heart at this time.
I am sorry.
It's over.
No, it's not.
It's not over.
Something can be done.
- Mother.
I want to
stay alone for a while.
Okay.
♪ Tell me whether
I am dead or alive. ♪
♪ Tell me that this is a dream,
not reality. ♪
♪ Tell me whether
I am dead or alive. ♪
♪ Tell me that this is a dream,
not reality. ♪
♪ I trusted you more than myself. ♪
♪ I considered you my life,
but you betrayed me. ♪
♪ Did I not love you enough? ♪
♪ How could you be so heartless? ♪
♪ How could you kill your love? ♪
♪ How could be so heartless?
Kill your love! ♪
♪ Tell me you're not
who you claim to be. ♪
♪ Tell me I will live longer. ♪
♪ If my body is cold,
why does my soul burn? ♪
♪ I am screaming,
but nobody hears me. ♪
♪ What pleasure did you get
from my pain? ♪
♪ How could you be so heartless?
So heartless. ♪
♪ How could you kill your love?
Kill your love. ♪
♪ How could you be so heartless?
So heartless! Kill your love! ♪
♪ How could you kill your love? ♪
♪ How could you be so heartless?
How could you kill your love? ♪
♪ How could you be so heartless? ♪
♪ How could you kill your love? ♪
Mom, why are you here?
How could I leave you alone?
I left you alone once.
And see what happened.
Mom.
How can we see each other?
How can we hear each other?
Oh my God!
Mom,
what did you do?
How?
'Gayatri, it's impossible.'
'It's a crazy plan.'
'Do you know what you are saying?'
'I don't...'
I' can't do this.
- Sanjeev.'
'Think like a doctor, '
'not a friend.'
'I am donating my heart to someone,
who needs it the most.'
'Gayatri, this is suicide!'
'I won't let you do it!'
'And you know that
even if you commit suicide, '
'I won't perform the surgery.'
'This is a murder!'
'This is not murder.'
'What happened inside
the operation theatre was murder.'
'You have to do this...'
'For me.
'Are you listening? Gayatri!'
'Gayatri!'
You were right about Ria.
She betrayed me.
I know.
How did you come to know about Ria?
When Trehan told me over the phone
that he had seen Ria somewhere...
'You...'
- He had seen Ria in Abu Dhabi with Sam
at a medical convention.
She was a member of his team.
And then,
when your medicines fell from her bag,
I became more suspicious.
Ria did everything cleverly.
But she made one mistake.
She left her bag with me.
'And when I opened her bag, '
'I found her correspondence
with the medical college'
'where she was a junior doctor.'
'I also found some credit cards'
'in the name of Shruti Tandon.'
I feel so bad.
I always considered Dr Trehan wrong.
Gayatri!
Oh God!
Prepare for the operation!
Send me the stretcher immediately!
- Yes, sir.
Dr Trehan,
I tried hard to save him, but...
I know how hard you tried.
Just get out of here.
The police are on their way.
- Come on, guys.
Come on, Sam, let's go.
- Come on, Sam, let's get going.
Come back, Adi.
Please.
I am so sorry.
Dr Sameer Saxena,
it's due to doctors like you
that the entire medical fraternity
is infamous.
'Remove my heart after I die, '
'it belongs to someone else.'
'Make sure it doesn't burn with me.'
Gayatri,
this is the most difficult moment
of my life.
I will never forgive you for this.
Sam.
Ria, it's all over.
You must leave.
The police will be here any moment now.
Sam, I don't need to go anywhere.
I married him.
Remember? I am his widow.
I will still get my share.
What!
But he is alive, Ria.
He isn't dead.
If he hasn't died, he will soon.
Excuse me, Mrs Singh.
Just a minute.
Okay. Cut it.
Congratulations, sir.
Well done.
- Great job, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Well done.
Oh my God!
He is sinking.
Start DE-fibrillation!
Quick!
- Clear.
Not responding.
- Make it 150 joules.
Clear.
- 200 joules.
200 joules!
- 200 joules. Clear.
It's about time, Adi.
You should go now.
No, mom.
I don't want to go back.
First, I lost dad.
And now I have lost you.
Sam and Ria betrayed me.
No, Adi.
Don't say that.
Every person has his own journey.
Just being with someone for a while
doesn't mean you go on the same journey.
Until now we were together.
We were with each other.
But now you need to
embark upon your journey.
That's what life is all about.
I don't want such a life.
I want to be with you.
I won't go back.
You don't get it, Adi.
Even if you don't go back,
you can't be with me.
We were meant to be together
only for so long.
Clear.
No... No response.
- Clear.
I want to show you something.
Adi.
- 'Dad, I want to sail the boat too.'
'I want you to stop blaming yourself'
'for your dad's death.'
'How long will you hold him, Gayatri?'
'Let him live his life.'
'Come, Adi.
- It was an accident.'
'Just an accident.'
'Come my brave-heart. Sit here.
- It was not your fault.'
'Now you're the captain of the boat.'
'Do what you want.'
'Vikram, don't make him sit
so close to the bow. I am scared.'
'Relax, Gayatri.'
'No, it's too fast.
- He will be fine.'
'Adi!'
'Dad, save me!
- Adi!'
'Dad, help me!
'Adi!'
'Adi!
- Help me.'
'Vikram, save him!'
'Dad, I am drowning! Save me!'
'Vikram!'
'Hold him!'
'Adi, go.
Adi, come on! Come up!'
'Vikram!
- Gayatri!'
'No!
'Dad!
- Vikram!'
'I am sorry, dad. Please forgive me.'
'I am responsible for this.'
Your dad sacrificed his life
to save you.
You need to go back, Adi.
Every mother give birth
to her child once,
but I am the most fortunate of all,
for getting a chance
to give birth to you once again.
Don't take this away from me.
You've to go back.
'I still remember the vent
in that small room'
'from where the moonlight used to
filter into the room.'
'I used to sleep on mom's lap, '
'when she would sing a lullaby.'
- My son.
'I lost that childhood somewhere'
'when I grew up.'
'Today, I feel a lump in my throat'
'when I recall those moments.'
'Tears roll down my eyes as I wonder
why mom doesn't scold me anymore.'
'Have your food on time.'
'Come home early.'
'Why doesn't she say that?'
'Where am I?'
'Why did I go away from mom?'
'Why do I feel so helpless?'
'Today, my sorrow knows no bounds.'
'The small wound has become incurable.'
'I will fall asleep recalling
her stories, '
'and her loving pats on my head.'
'It seems as if'
'mom will come to me.'
'She will embrace me.'
'And she will take me
to the world of angels.'
'Where there will be a king.'
'And a queen.'
'A a new story will end.'
'Mom will go back quietly.'
'I know'
'mom won't come back.'
Congratulations, Adi.
Welcome back.
Adi!
Adi, my sweetheart.
Thank God you are here.
I was so worried for you.
As soon as I got the news of
your discharge from the hospital,
I went to your house.
But I got to know that you're here.
I missed you so much.
I heard about mother.
I am so sorry.
She was very happy for us.
We became quite close
when we were in the hospital.
I miss her.
Had she been here,
she wouldn't have let them arrest me.
Can you imagine?
Sam did all that.
I mean, he was so close to you.
He was your friend.
How could he?
And now he refuses to
cooperate with the police.
They arrested me too because of him.
But they didn't have evidence.
Thanks to the Governor
who stood surety for me,
otherwise I wouldn't have got bail.
Now that you have recovered,
everything will be fine.
Everything will be okay, right?
Adi, I hope
you don't think I was involved...
Of course not.
Ria, I know everything.
I heard everything
in the operation theatre.
I seemed to be unconscious,
but I was wide awake.
Anaesthesia Awareness.
You would know about it.
After all, you were a doctor
on Sam's team.
What do you know?
You don't know anything.
People like you don't
know the difference
between staying alive and living it up.
You didn't even want to live.
I taught you how to live.
Adi, you were dead.
I only tried to kill someone
who was already dead.
Besides, what proof do you have?
Who will believe you?
People think you were unconscious.
'There are some crimes
that cannot be pardoned.'
'I have got the punishment I deserved.'
'I could have got Ria punished as well, '
'but I want you to do it.'
'I am sending you the proof.'
'Forgive me if you can. Sam.'
Adi, please don't send me back to jail.
Adi, you love me. Please.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Ria, I would have forgiven you,
but you destroyed the heart
that was in love with you.
And I have my mom's heart now.
Think about it.
Can my mom ever forgive you?
Adi! Please!
Leave me.
Adi, forgive me.
Subtitle by Vishal & Jio
'A boy was madly in love with a girl.'
'One day the girl said
'If you love me so much, '
'go and bring your mom's heart to me.'
'When the boy asked his mom
for her heart, '
'she gave it to him with a smile.'
'When the boy was rushing
to the girl with his mom's heart, '
'he tripped and fell on the ground.'
'The mom's heart in his hands asked, '
'Son, I hope you didn't hurt yourself.'
'I had heard the story in childhood, '
'but I understood it now.'
♪ When I went out in the world
looking for faithfulness, ♪
♪ I realised that I had
the wrong address. ♪
♪ When I went out in the world
looking for faithfulness, ♪
♪ The one whose arrival
had fulfilled my life. ♪
♪ It'd brought happiness at my door
and filled every void of my life. ♪
♪ Why did she punish me for no reason? ♪
♪ Why did she shatter my dreams? ♪
♪ She hurt me bad
and made my life miserable. ♪
♪ I was looking for divinity
in her heart. ♪
♪ I realised I was looking for it
in the wrong place. ♪
♪ When I went out in the world
looking for faithfulness, ♪
♪ The one I kept looking
for every moment, ♪
♪ My days and nights are agonising
without her. ♪
♪ All I have are her memories.
I hope she doesn't take those away. ♪
♪ I don't know where
to look for her now. ♪
♪ When I tried to find a reason to live. ♪
♪ I realised I had no clue. ♪
♪ When I went out in the world
looking for faithfulness... ♪