24,000
[ Woman Screaming ]
[ Murmuring ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
The Culann tribe pledges a bond
by blood oath...
with our new allies.
Let neither man nor spirit
tear the fabric of this unification.
Together we will purge
the Roman vermin from our island...
and unite in your father's
memory, Conor.
[ Speaking Gaelic ]
[ All ]
Through fire with wrath.
for our homeland. to the death.
[ Woman Screaming ]
That's the banshee's wail. lad.
Her cry foretells death.
- Whose?
- Mine.
Yours. We don't know.
But someone will die,
and soon.
Through fire with wrath.
for our homeland...
to the death.
[ Banshee Screaming ]
[ Man Narrating ]
Long ago,
at the edge of the known world,
the last Celtic tribes
were fighting for survival.
Europe had fallen
to the Romans,
and this remote
and untamed island...
was the final stronghold
of the ancient ways.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[ Roaring ]
[ Conor ]
What does this banshee look like?
No one has ever seen one.
but two nights. two deaths.
and the banshee's wail
was heard before each.
I worry for who might be next.
[ Man ]
There won't be a next.
This is Morvern.
His father died last night...
at the hands of Roman assassins.
After hearing the banshee's wail.
This demon has cursed us too long.
You're going to hunt it?
Burn it to ashes.
The banshee doesn't cause death.
It foretells it.
You agreed to unite
against all our enemies.
Have you forgotten
your pledge?
Conor.
This is a mistake.
We made a pledge.
We can't back out now.
The banshee moves
quicker than the wind.
It can't be caught.
Then it will be a short hunt.
[ Man ]
Legend tells us this beast cloaks itself
in darkness, and may move as we do.
But beware. It can also take on
any form it chooses.
How do we kill it?
With this poison.
For my father.
I miss my father too.
but he wouldn't want this.
He wouldn't be here.
[ Chattering ]
I want the first shot.
Take it.
[ Banshee Screams ]
There it is! Go!
[ Chattering ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Grunts ]
- No!
- Oh!
- That's a woman!
- You heard the wail.
- Of a frightened woman.
- The druid said it could take any form.
Let her speak.
Explain yourself.
- She's afraid.
- She's the banshee. It's the same sound
we heard before my father died.
- How can we be sure of that?
- It can take any form. Stand aside.
- What if we're wrong?
- Then it seems the banshee calls for you.
Perhaps she calls for you.
I'm not gonna let her die.
It can take any form.
She looks like a girl to me.
We'll take her.
What?
If you think she's a banshee.
we'll take her.
The curse will be on us.
Fine.
If we see her in our midst again.
it'll be your head.
You won't.
My father is dead because of her.
Leave it. Morvern. Leave it!
But she's the banshee!
Keep your eyes on the trail.
Roman assassins are everywhere.
How come she's so quiet?
[ Fergus ]
Have you lost your mind?
[ Conor]
If she is a banshee. then like you said.
we must respect her.
Respect doesn't include
asking her to supper.
[ Rustling ]
We couldn't-
We couldn't
just let her die. Fergus.
So instead we bring
the voice of death home with us.
She could be a Roman spy.
Pretending to be a banshee?
She needs our help. Fergus.
I promised Galen I'd take in
anyone who was in need.
Galen is dead.
And I'm in charge now.
if that's all right with you.
Sure-
if the Romans don't kill us too.
[ Waves Crashing ]
I need more men.
Rome can't spare
any more battalions.
How do you expect me to take this
pitiful rock without proper support?
By winning hearts and minds
one tribe at a time.
Convince them your way is superior.
Negotiate? With these barbarians?
Unite them behind you.
Impossible.
If you don't,
there is someone who will.
Leave us.
- If you're referring to that boy-
- His goal is to gather the tribes...
and try to protect his land
from invasion.
You represent Rome.
If he's successful. we will never
find what we came here for.
All the more reason
to show our strength.
Show them your charm first.
We need the spear.
It's on this island.
And after 400 years of searching for it.
you'll forgive me if I'm a bit impatient.
I want it as much as you do.
Then you can't kill everyone.
But you can seduce them.
If one of the tribes has the spear.
do you think they're just
gonna hand it over?
You can be very persuasive.
I had a good teacher.
She won't eat. She hasn't slept.
I'm worried about her.
You got a family or a village?
We can take you to a safe place.
It's a sanctuary. and it's our home.
You'd be protected there.
[ Woman ]
No.!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Fergus ] Conor.!
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Fergus ]
Take cover.! Catlin, down.!
[ Arrows Whooshing ]
Morvern. Traitorous bastard.
I thought they were allies.
Welcome to politics. lad.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
- [ Woman Grunts ]
- She's got him.
- [ Woman Grunting ]
- [ Arrows Whooshing ]
Attack!
Attack this. ribbon head.
[ Shouting ]
[ Grunting. Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans. Spits ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Spits ]
[ Unsheathes Sword ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
Where's that bastard Morvern?
Where's-
It's all right. It's all right.
We were ambushed.
Morvern and eight assassins.
- Did they kill her?
- Not quite.
You were hit.
She took out the poison.
[ Groans ]
I owe you my life.
I swear that I'll never have yours.
I don't know how they could have
mistaken you for a banshee.
You're a life-giver.
Does our life-giver have a name?
Shannon.
[ Shannon ]
Catlin?
I haven't thanked you yet.
You defended me.
Somebody had to.
Why?
The Culann saw a banshee.
I've had fits since I was a child.
Some people think I'm a demon.
Some think it's dark magic.
It's just who I am.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Fergus ]
Get that broth down you, lad.
- Where are you going?
- You've all been very kind. but I can't stay.
You have to.
The Culann tribe will kill you.
[ Sheep Bleats ]
The Romans kill the spotted ones.
[ Bleating Continues ]
When I was a slave.
I used to have to help them.
They killed the ones
that were different.
But when I came here
and saw that one.
I knew I didn't have to be afraid.
Stay.
Not a good night to eat alone.
Friend. we're in danger
and need aid.
A banshee stalks these woods.
Have you seen it?
Its wail portends death.
[ Footsteps ]
- Who's hungry?
-If you've seen anything. you best tell us.
This should rouse him.
[ Grunting ]
[ Cracking ]
[ Wheezing ]
You ruined my dinner.
[ Screams ]
[ Groans ]
[ Arrows Hit Ground ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Wheezing ]
[ Man ]
Let's get out ofhere.!
Go.!
[ Men Shouting ]
I want to find to find this banshee.
[ Diana ]
An infantile myth.
It was real enough for them
to want to kill it.
What else do these people
have to do?
Look at this message.
It's six months old.
Rome could be sacked
and burning for all we know.
The banshee foretells death.
Diana.
It's a superstition!
Superstition is rooted in truth.
"Prohibit all local holidays.''
They actually think I work for them.
- I can't afford to dismiss this.
- I can.
[ Gasps ]
Then you dismiss me.
How do you explain what I am?
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
There you go.
There you go. All right.
You're doing great.
This way.
Let's go now.Just about there.
You'll be fine.
I hope your child
isn't cursed with your looks.
Better mine than yours.
[ Chuckles ]
Watch your head.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
So Conor tells me you've drunk
all the ale on the island
twice over. True?
No. Thrice over.
That's how I get to the other world.
You don't like it here?
Ale fills the belly
when there's no food to be had.
It numbs the pain?
Some.
But not all?
We're mutually afflicted. it seems.
No one could have saved
Conor's family. Fergus.
Not even you.
Conor's told you too much.
He didn't have to.
I'm sorry if I've upset you.
It's not you. lass.
It's the weight.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
It's all right.
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Shrieks. Screams ]
[ Fergus ]
Conor.!
[ Screaming Continues ]
Dead.
My child was born dead.
- [ Screaming Continues ]
- [ Conor ] Shannon?
[ Chattering ]
[ Whimpering ]
This was your doing.
- You brought her here.
- She saved his life.
Tell that to my dead child.
[ Man ]
That's right.
She didn't harm your baby.
If the child was meant to die.
it was gonna happen
whether she was here or not.
- You promised us we'd be safe here.
- You are safe.
He's our leader.
We abide with his decision-
whether we agree with it or not.
- What good is a leader who can't be trusted?
- I want her out.
- [ Man ] Me too.
- There are people hunting her.
- If she's found. they're gonna-
- If she stays. the Romans will find us.
They'll hear her screams,
then we'll all be dead.
Get her out. Conor.
or I'll kill her myself.
- You're not thinking clearly.
- My baby's dead.
[ Shannon Whimpering ]
All right. She'll go.
And I'll go with her.
What stout decision
awaits us next?
I thought I'd find
the answer here.
Galen said when all things
were balanced. when all was right.
you could hear the power
in the land.
And it moves through you.
gives you clarity.
He called it the Roar.
I haven't heard it since he left.
Maybe you should be listening
to someone else.
I couldn't just send her off
by herself. Fergus.
- Why don't you talk to her?
She may have the answer.
- What do you mean?
She sees things that others can't.
Did you tell her about what happened
with me and your family?
No.
Talk to her.
[ Sighs ]
This is my fault.
A banshee must never interfere
with a foretold death.
You didn't interfere.
Finnegas's child is gone.
I'm not talking about the child.
Me?
That arrow was meant to kill you.
I saw it in a vision.
Then why did you save me?
Because you saved me.
And I didn't want to see you die.
and I still don't.
But I'm all right. I-
You don't understand.
The vision hasn't gone away.
Please go home.
You should be with the people
that you love.
If I'm to die.
it won't be because of you.
[ Sniffling ]
Where do you come from?
Tell me.
A village to the north.
Let me take you there.
Please.
Morvern's after you.
and I don't want
to see you die either.
No outsider has ever been
to my village.
We don't have to go in.
I just want to make sure
you get there safely.
You've lost more than your family.
Haven't you?
A woman.
Yes. Her name was Claire.
Did you love her?
Very much.
She watches you
from the other world.
Is she happy?
She's free.
[ Waves Crashing ]
[ Bird Warbles ]
[ Screams ]
Guard!
How long have I been
sitting in the dark?
Since the sun set. my queen.
And still no sign of Longinus?
Not as yet. my queen.
I am your queen. aren't I?
What if we were in Rome?
Then I would have to answer
to the emperor.
Yes. you would.
Does the emperor dance?
Uh. I'm sure he does.
Would you dance with the emperor
if he asked you to?
Uh. I-I suppose I would.
I'm sure he's a very good dancer.
I dropped something.
Would you mind retrieving it for me?
No. Of course not.
Uh. where is it?
Out there.
Out... the window?
If you got up on the ledge.
I'm sure you'd see it.
[ Sighs ]
You'd do it for the emperor.
- What is it I'm looking for?
- A wine pitcher.
All I can see is the ocean.
Oh. I'm sure it's out there somewhere.
Longinus?
Longinus. you bastard!
[ Waves Crashing ]
I hate drinking alone.
Mmm.
- Stardust.
- You are a magician.
Galen taught me that.
He must have thought a lot of you.
I'll never be the magician he was.
How do you know?
Your path may be charmed.
Charmed.
I like that.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Groans ]
Is it happening again?
The vision?
- What can I do?
- Nothing. I just need to sleep.
[ Sighs ]
It's too beautiful.
Do I frighten you?
No.
You foretell death.
I haven't seen your passing.
But others may have.
Others?
Please.
I have lived five lifetimes
in the hope of finding salvation.
For one terrible sin.
I've been cursed forever.
You're the Roman centurion
who killed his God.
Yes.
You seek the spear that bled him.
You pray it will end your life.
If I could just know
that death was possible.
it would...
ease my burden.
Please.
You must promise
not to harm anyone-
none of my friends.
I'll know if you lie.
You have my word.
[ Water Splashing ]
They're headed for Mount Cassair.
They say
that demons rule up there.
They haven't met us yet.
[ Doors Creak ]
We've waited many years for you.
Then you know why I've come.
Yes. We understand.
Like you. a single act has cursed us.
My ancestors were known
for their beautiful hair.
They'd never cut it.
And it would grow
the length of their bodies.
From sunrise to sunset.
the eldest daughter
would comb her hair.
It's said she preferred
to tend to her locks...
than to the needs
ofher husband and child.
One day her infant daughter
drowned in the lake.
So obsessed had she been
with her vanity. that she hadn't
heard the child's cries.
From that day on.
all the women of the clan...
and every daughter born to them...
would forever be haunted
by visions of death.
And no one has ever seen me
in their vision?
I'm sorry.
[ Inhales ]
The mists in these hills
can reveal a man's worst fears.
[ Shannon ]
They're not real.
Just images meant to frighten you.
[ Tully ]
Images of what?
[ Shannon ]
Follow me closely.
[ Fergus ]
Tully? Tully?
[ Derek ]
Coward.!
Derek?
I trusted you
to look after my son.
You were my champion!
But you were drunk. and you let me die!
[ Claire ]
Conor.
Claire?
You could have saved me.
I didn't have to die.
No. Claire. please-
She's not real. Conor.
I didn't have to die.
That's your voice. not hers.
[ Grunts ]
Just me. lad.
It's not real.
- Fergus?
- [ Grunts ]
If it's not real. why did they hear me?
Get her out of here.
Fergus!
- Way ahead of you. boy.
- [ Shouting ]
รถ[ Woman Singing Ballad ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
รถ[ Ends ]
Think he'll come back?
Doubtful.
Imagine the things he saw.
Well. come on. lads.
We've got to catch up with the ladies.
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Banshees Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
What is it?
They won't let me in.
Why?
When I saved your life.
I broke with custom.
and now they won't help me.
And nothing can help you.
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Banshees Screaming ]
Can't we appeal to them?
[ Screaming Continues ]
Please. You have to take her in.
Her life is in danger.
Mother.
[ Sobbing ]
Be still. child.
Please help us.
- I can't.
- Why?
Once we've seen a vision.
we can't veer from its path.
So he must die?
Forget about me.
You've seen him?
And delayed his death.
I know it was wrong.
What?
Please. tell me. Mother. if there's anything
that can be done for him- anything.
There is a way. isn't there?
Do you know of the River Tannas?
- It runs through the next valley.
- What's there?
Some believe one of our ancestors
drank from the water.
And the curse was removed?
Everything she knew.
everything she saw...
was washed away.
and some were spared.
- How do we find it?
- I know where it is.
Thank you. Mother.
[ Both Sobbing ]
I love you. Shannon.
[ Waves Crashing ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
So? Did you find your banshee?
And was she all you'd hoped for?
Longinus. there's just
one answer for you.
The spear.
Me.
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Insects Buzzing ]
Ah. sweet Bridget smiles on us all.
My only sadness
is that when you drink the water.
you'll forget us.
I'll know you again soon.
You are a true champion.
The land's fertile enough
without your tears. Fergus.
Don't spoil the moment.
Your path
will always be charmed. Tully.
Remember that.
- The land is fertile enough without-
- Be quiet. Fergus.
I have no words for you.
Your selflessness-
No one has ever given me so much.
[ Sighs ]
Let's begin your new life.
[ Gasps ]
Shannon!
No.!
[ Grunts ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Groaning Continues ]
No. It's pierced her heart.
- She'll die.
- She was meant to.
It was me.
It was supposed to be me.
Your mother-
Your mother sent us here.
She knew.
Because she knew it was right.
How can this be right?
[ Shannon Gasping ]
- [ Roaring In Distance ]
- Listen.
- [ Roaring Continues ]
- [ Exhales ]
[ Roaring Intensifies ]
Now it's my time to be free.
[ Roaring Continues ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Waves Crashing ]
[ Seagull Mewing ]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org