Wake up, please.
Mummy, I want water.
Mummy...
Mummy.
Mamma, where is papa?
Mamma, let's go outside.
Mamma I'm coming, okay.
(TV Background Noise)
Papa.
Papa!
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Eight...
Three... four...
Six...
Eight.
Nine... ten...
Nineteen.
Papa!
Mamma I can't reach up there.
Bapu!
One... two... three...
Mamma...
Mamma, the water is running.
The water is running.
Mamma, dancing.
Come, Mamma.
Mamma, come.
Mamma, today's paper.
Paper.
Bapu's photo is torn.
Mamma... Bapu.
I want to play on the swing.
Mamma, get up, please!
Mummy.
Mamma, get up, please.
Please come Mamma..
Mummy.
Mamma..
Mamma, this is your daily soap.
Come, Mamma.
Watch TV.
Come on, Mamma.
Mamma.
Come, Mamma.
Mamma, get up.
Mummy...
Mummy.
Mamma.
Phone...
Mamma, where is the phone?
Mamma, I want to do potty.
Mamma.
Potty on my finger.
Phone.
The phone is ringing.
Mamma, phone.
Hello.
Phone.
Papa's slippers are wet.
Mamma, papa's slippers are wet.
Take it, Mummy.
Mummy.
Mummy, take it.
Oh ho.
Mummy. Mummy.
Pihu is naked.
Mamma help Pihu wear pajamas.
Mamma.
Mamma, what is this?
Mamma, see medicines.
Mamma, can I eat this?
Look, Mamma.
Mamma.
Mamma, can I eat this?
Can I eat this?
Phone.
Mamma.
Mamma, phone.
Oh...
Chucking the phone
won't prove anything, Puja.
Mummy.
Why don't you get some help?
Idiot! You've made my life hell.
Actually, I'm not interested in
talking to you either. Understand?
I just called to say...
that I'm going to miss
my flight again because of you.
You didn't pack my bags
or iron my clothes.
You knew I had an
important meeting in Kolkata.
What difference does it make to you?
Even if someone's
flying out in the morning...
you still want to butt heads.
Hello. Puja?
Are you listening?
Mummy.
Okay.
Just go to hell!
And listen, I forgot to turn
off the iron in a hurry.
And it's entirely your fault.
You females are the
worst thing in any man's life!
Whether you live or die...
I don't care about you at all.
But Pihu's at home.
So see to it that you turn it off.
And what's wrong with Pihu?
Why is she crying?
Hello. Pihu.
- Hello.
- Papa.
Pihu.
- Pihu my love.
- Papa, mamma is here only.
Papa, I am coming. Yes, dear...
Papa is going to Kolkata. Hello.
Pihu.
My love. Give papa a kiss.
Come on.
Okay, bye.
Hello, Puja.
Hello.
Damn it!
Mamma is hurt.
Mamma needs cream.
Mamma, where is the cream?
Gaurav, I fought with my folks to
marry you, but what did I get from you?
You said, you'll return
home only after I'm dead
I am going away
I wanted to take Pihu along,
but I didn't have the guts to do it.
Goodbye - Puja.
Look at me now.
Mummy.
Look, the peacock took the peahen away.
What little was left, the thief took away.
Stop being angry, let's get back to play,
cheer up girl, throw all sadness away.
Mamma, sing the rhyme for me.
This is my cream. These are my hands.
See my hands.
What do I have in my hands?
Cream. Look Mamma, cream on my hands.
See, Mamma.
Mamma, smoke.
Mamma, where is the smoke coming from?
Mamma, can I turn this off?
How did it happen?
Mamma, where is the smoke coming from?
Mamma!
Mummy!
Mamma, I want milk.
Get up, Mamma.
Please get up.
Mamma!
Oh no...
One. Two. Three. Four.
Pihu's bread.
Stop. Please.
Mummy!
Mamma!
Any trash?
Madam, any trash?
Pihu is coming.
I am eating jam.
Wait, I am coming.
Eat... come on, eat.
You must eat your food...
Eat.
Eat...
Mummy..
Mummy, you must eat.
Go on, eat. Take...
Come on, eat.
Eat.
One-two-three.
What are you saying?
Bomb, Bomb, Bomb.
Mummy.
Hello.
Pihu, - Hello, papa.
Baby, where is Mamma.
Give the phone to Mamma.
Mamma. Papa's phone.
What happened, mamma?
Puja.
- I've boarded the airplane.
- Excuse me, sir.
I'm calling from
the airplane's toilet.
My phone will be switched
off for two hours.
I just wanted to ask whether
you turned off the iron or not?
You know that...
- the iron's automatic function isn't working.
- 'Excuse me, sir.'
Hello.
Hello, Puja. Talk to me.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Hello.
Excuse me, sir.
Please come out, sir.
- Phones are not allowed, sir.
- That's the problem with you.
You have a very short temper.
Fine, I admit I was late yesterday.
I couldn't be on time
for Pihu's birthday.
But did we have to
argue over it all night?
- Switch off your phone sir.
- Yeah, just two minutes.
And why did you drag
Meera in our argument?
Who the hell is Meera between us?
You know she's just a colleague.
And she's your friend, not mine.
Phones are not allowed, sir.
- Please, sir.
- Hello.
Hello.
Hello...
Hello!
Mamma, the phone's turned off.
This is Pihu's phone.
Mummy.
Uff...
Madam, milk.
Wait, coming.
Pinky, call the guard.
These guys at 903 are driving me nuts.
What do you want? Hello, madam.
- Guard!
- What's the matter?
- None of the doorbells are working, madam?
No electricity?
The generator's getting fixed.
Power supply will be restored soon.
See, power's back.
I just wanted to know...
What did you break this time, Pinky?
Have the people in 804 gone out?
I had brought cow's
milk for the child.
- But no one's opening the door.
- How the hell would I know?
Check with the guard. Go.
They kept partying all night.
I couldn't sleep a wink.
Are they still sleeping? At this hour?
How would I know?
That is not our problem.
Pinky!
- I thought since you're their neighbor,
- Pinky!
You would know.
What neighbor!
We didn't even get
invited to the party.
Damn you!
Madam, can you please
hand over this milk to them?
Go give it to the people in 705.
Such a temper is not good
I am only doing my job.
You didn't have to yell at me.
Mummy!
Guard. Guard.
Yes.
See what's the commotion all about.
This place is not
fit to live in anymore.
- Okay, I'll take a look.
- Hurry up.
Mamma!
Come out, Mamma.
Oww!
Mamma, I want to play.
I'll see you, Mummy.
Amogh! Listen, Amogh.
Amogh.
Ishika.
Amogh, see Pihu's doll.
Amogh.
Amogh isn't speaking to me.
Mamma, come out.
Amogh.
Ishika.
Aarav is always after me.
Aarav.
He's not speaking to me.
Ishika, see Pihu's doll.
Listen, Amogh.
Damn!
Shameless people!
No manners at all.
Damn, Damn.
They have money...
but when will
they learn some sense?
Oh-oh!
It hurts.
A cut.
I am hurt.
I'll fall.
Mummy.
Mamma.
Get up, please.
Ishika, bring Pihu's doll.
Listen, Amogh Bring Pihu's doll.
Amogh, Ishika.
Bring Pihu's doll.
Amogh.
No. No. No, baby.
Get down, baby.
Whose child is that?
Is anyone listening?
Look where she's standing?
Aunty, Pihu's doll.
What are you saying, baby?
Pihu's doll.
What?
Aunty will bring the doll, baby.
Pihu's doll.
Where is your mamma, baby?
Mamma sleeping.
Call your Mamma. Go to your mamma.
Get down.
Hello! Is anybody there?
Is anyone watching her?
Pihu's doll.
Yes, baby. Aunty will get your doll.
Get down. Get down, baby.
Hey guard, why don't you
go up and check on that kid.
Someone check on her.
Baby, down. Get down.
Pihu's doll.
Down, baby. Very good.
Good girl.
Mamma plane.
Mamma papa's home.
Mamma come out.
Hey Puja, this is Meera.
I know you're not talking today.
But why do you keep
behaving like this?
What's gotten into you?
I am very happy with my married life.
You know that.
Hello, are you listening?
Listen, I am coming over to see you.
Mamma, what is aunty saying?
I am coming over
without your permission.
- What is aunty saying?
- Hello.
Hello.
Pihu.
M... M...
Love you. See you soon.
I was calling.
Which aunty is this?
Aunty.
- Guard.
- Yes.
Why is the power supply fluctuating?
It will blow a fuse.
The generator's still
getting fixed, madam.
Power will be restored shortly.
Mamma, what is this?
Pihu is crying.
Mummy, look..
When I was a little baby.
See... little baby.
Little baby gets a kiss.
When I was a little baby.
Mamma, Papa has come home.
Papa has come home.
Pintu, Pintu.
Send your brother down.
To help me carry this stuff.
Papa...
Its papa... Papa's picture.
Hello.
Puja... Puja I am...
- Pihu.
- Hello.
Pihu. Pihu.
Give the phone to your mamma, baby.
Papa has to go for a meeting.
Give her the phone now.
Stop playing with the phone, baby.
The line will get disconnected.
Please...
Mamma sleeping.
What are you saying, baby?
Mamma's sleeping.
Where is Papa?
Papa...
Papa's in Kolkata, baby.
- Mamma's in Kolkata.
- No baby, papa, not mamma.
Pihu. Will you do one thing for papa?
Hello. Pihu.
Come home, papa.
Yes, baby. Papa will come tomorrow.
Tell mamma... papa said...
Sorry.
What will you tell mamma, dear?
Will you tell mamma?
Sorry.
Okay, baby. Bye.
Papa's keeping the phone down now.
Papa will call back in one hour.
Okay, baby.
Papa loves you.
"Twinkle-Twinkle Little Star."
"Ring-a Ring-a Roses."
Meow, Tell me a story.
Meow-Meow.
Hello.
Good morning, madam.
Sorry. Good afternoon madam.
Am I talking to
Mrs. Puja Gupta Chaudhary?
Madam, I am speaking from
Bold and Beautiful Helpline.
We have a tie-up with
each and every beauty salon.
And we...
Mamma, say hello.
And we offer up-to-date services.
Like with an expensive hair-cut,
you'll get a bleach free.
And full body waxing plus...
Hello. Hello.
Can you hear me?
Why don't you hang up
if you're not interested?
Don't waste our time.
Look, Mamma.
Mamma... Get up.
Mamma, food.
Get up, please.
Mummy.
Can I drink milk?
Mamma, Pihu's milk.
Oh no.
Get up, please.
Mamma, feed me.
Mummy.
Oh ho.
Mamma.
It is all wet.
Mr. Gaurav.
Yes...
Anybody home?
Hello. Hello.
I guess no one's in.
Bunch of idiots.
They left the tap open.
This is so ridiculous...
We must complain about this.
Yes...
Even the power supply has
made our life hell today.
Yeah... it's getting difficult
to live here anymore.
Mr. Gaurav.
Let's go.
Get the generator fixed first.
Wait, I am coming.
Papa's calling...
Hello.
Papa, tell me a story.
Pihu.
Pihu, give the phone to Mamma.
Hello.
Hello, Pihu.
Pihu.
Papa, tell me a story first.
Yes, baby.
And a tiger came at night.
The tiger started
coming closer slowly.
He saw Noni.
And what did the tiger say?
Noni...
I will eat Noni's pony.
Pihu's coughing?
Go tell mamma to give you medicine.
- Papa, mamma's gone.
- What?
Mamma's gone?
Where did mamma go?
Pihu, call mamma.
Mamma's not here.
What are you saying, baby?
Where is Mamma?
Tell me where Mamma is.
Mamma's gone to Kolkata.
What, baby?
Papa's in Kolkata, baby.
Mamma is with you.
Mamma sleeping. Mamma sleeping.
Is Mamma is still sleeping, Pihu?
Go wake up Mamma.
Mamma sleeping. Mamma sleeping.
And say, Mamma good morning.
Pihu...
Mamma sleeping.
Go, baby.
Mamma sleeping. Mamma sleeping.
Pihu...
Go.
Go and wake her up.
S♪♪t
Driver...
- Stop the car on the side?
- On the side?
Yes.
But it's no parking.
I am telling you just stop here.
Mamma sleeping. Mamma sleeping.
Yes, baby. Papa heard you.
Go to mamma and don't hang up.
Pihu, did you hear?
Hello.
Where's my other phone?
Have you seen my other phone?
What?
S♪♪t
Pihu. Pihu, don't hang up.
Stay with papa.
Papa, mamma sleeping. Mamma sleeping.
I know, dear.
Just don't hang up.
Papa, come soon.
Yes, baby. Papa's coming.
Driver, take me to the airport.
- When are you coming?
- Papa's coming right now.
Stay on the line with papa.
Don't hang up.
Will you play with papa?
Papa...
Hello. Pihu.
Please drive faster, Driver.
I am.
You can see...
Oh kuhchi.
Oh kuchi.
Drive faster.
- Oh puchi.
Oh, honey.
- How long?
- What, sir?
How much longer to the airport?
One hour.
What? One hour.
Oh, Bunny.
- Please drive faster.
- Oh, Bunny.
Who is dad's baby?
Me!
Hey, this is Meera.
Sorry I can't take
your call right now.
Leave your message after the beep.
Hi, Meera.
You were supposed to meet Puja today.
Did you go see her?
Hope all is well there?
Hello?
Listen, can you do me a favor?
As soon as you get my
message please go to my home...
and call me immediately.
Hello. Meera.
You please drive faster.
What are you waiting for?
I am driving faster. You can see...
- See what?
- The roads.
It's jammed.
Kolkata - what a stupid city!
Hello, Pihu. Papa's coming home.
Go to Mamma.
Mamma is sleeping.
I'm not going to wake her up.
I will sit here.
Mamma, the phone is not working.
A fly is coming.
Eat?
Can I eat this?
The medicine is bitter.
Mamma, I want more.
Can I eat more?
Can I eat more, mamma?
I'm done.
I ate your bitter medicines.
I'm done Mamma.
- Did anyone call the fire brigade?
- Yes.
I knew something was wrong.
Why is the water coming out?
If I hadn't warned everyone...
then the fire would've
spread throughout the building.
Where is Gaurav?
You're a strong guy.
Break the door down.
He called the Police.
Why call the police?
He should've called the fire brigade.
I went to the guard.
Does anyone have a hammer?
Let's break the lock.
Let's everyone break
the door down together.
There's water coming out.
Show some courage, please.
I can't do this alone.
We have to call a few more guys.
You're a young man.
Yes... Come on.
Break it down.
- Let's push together.
- Yes.
You just make tall claims.
- Does anyone know where Gaurav is?
- God knows.
He's on the way. He's coming.
When will he get here?
I called him. He said he's coming.
They were partying all night.
Gaurav's here.
Let Gaurav through.
Puja...
Pihu...
No.. no.. no..
Puja...
Puja, I am sorry.
Pihu...
Papa...
- Papa.
- Yes, baby.
Pihu.
Papa.
Pihu, where are you?
Papa is home, baby.
Papa.
Pihu.
- See Papa, Pihu's home.
- Yes...
I built both the houses.
Papa, wake up mamma.
I'm making a beautiful home.